<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>DEF CON Announcements!</title>
        <link>https://www.defcon.org/</link>
        <description>DEFCON is the world's largest annual hacker convention, held every year in Las Vegas, Nevada. The first DEFCON took place in June 1993. DEF CON is renowned for the "arcane arts" of drinking, socializing, debugging, and crowd control. DEFCON is what you make of it, so get involved and help the community grow.
This Feed will keep you up to date with some announcements surrounding pre and post con events, references to DEFCON in the news, and other errata. For the most up to date information visit or subscribe to the rss feeds on the forums (https://forum.defcon.org/) See https://www.defcon.org/ for more details, discussion forums, past speeches, and planning for the next year.</description>
        <generator>Feeder 2.5.9(1914); Mac OS X Version 10.10.3 (Build 14D131) http://reinventedsoftware.com/feeder/</generator>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>©1992-2014 DEF CON Communications, Inc. All Rights Reserved except for non-commercial educational purposes only. email if you have questions.</copyright>
        <managingEditor>dtangent@defcon.org (The Dark Tangent)</managingEditor>
        <webMaster>dtangent@defcon.org</webMaster>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:09:56 -0700</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:09:56 -0700</lastBuildDate>
        <category domain="http://www.dmoz.org/">Computers/Hacking</category>
        <image>
            <url>https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/dc-rss.png</url>
            <title>DEF CON Announcements!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/</link>
            <width>88</width>
            <height>88</height>
        </image>
        <atom:link href="https://www.defcon.org/defconrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title>Announcing the DEF CON Demo Lab</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-demolab.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="images/defcon-23/post-images/demolabs.jpg" alt="demo lab image"></a>

<p>Announcing yet another cool way you can participate in DEF CON: the DEF CON Demo Lab!</p>

<p>New for DEF CON 23 we are adding an place for you to show off your tools, projects, and tech to attendees - much like a poster board session but with computers.</p>

<p>The DEF CON Demo Lab is a dedicated area for hackers to show off what they have been working on, to answer questions, and even convert attendees into trying of giving feedback on their projects.</p>

<p>Presenters will be given a dedicated time and location to present a tool or project of their creation; show what it does, how it works, and why we need it in our arsenal.</p>

<p>Got something you’re itching to share? Get involved! </p>

<p>Full details at: <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-demolab.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-demolab.html</a></p>

]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:09:56 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FF11E110-5B84-41B2-B15F-B2A4B48F9596</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 23 Call for Workshops!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cftraining.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/cfw.jpg" alt="call for workshops image">

<p>On the 3rd floor of Ballys South tower, The Jubilee Tower, lay seven rooms [1], each one 1,400 sq feet. That's enough space for about 55 people in classroom format. What to do with all that space away from the main action of the convention? I've wanted to try workshops and trainings for years but we have never had the room once we filled up the Rio. Now we finally have some space at the new hotels so I am calling on the community to tell us what we should do with the rooms.</p> 

<p>Check out the <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cftraining.html">Call for Workshops</a> for full details!</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 22:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">933582B7-1FB4-4F72-A62B-4648FF53369A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON Villages make an appearance at the Tribeca Film Festival!</title>
            <link>https://tribecafilm.com/festival/springstudios</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/tribeca.jpg" alt="tribeca film festival image"></a>

<p>For the first time ever, DEF CON is teaming up with the Tribeca Film Festival to bring a few of its famous Villages to New York. The Villages – interactive spaces stocked with gear, projects and brilliant humans – immerse the visitor in particular nodes of hacker culture. Hands-on activities, eye-opening presentations and open-ended experimentation combine to bring out the hacker in everyone.</p>

<p>Join us April 23 - April 25th, 2015 in Studio X of Spring Studios and you will:</p>

<p>• Learn to pick a lock in the Lock Picking Village.</p>

<p>• Make your devices and identity more secure by seeing how the bad guys operate in the Privacy/Crypto Village.</p>

<p>• Study the noble art of voiding all your warranties in the Hardware Hacking Village.</p>

<p>• Get schooled in the hacker's most important skill in the Social Engineering Village.</p>

<p>• Discover what it takes to open that weird security envelope without leaving a trace in the Tamper-Evident Village.</p>


<p><a href="https://tribecafilm.com/festival/springstudios">https://tribecafilm.com/festival/springstudios</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 15:33:35 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3C836EEC-E9B8-4532-B954-58F2C13B01F5</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New DEF CON 23 Call for Suites!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cfsuites.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img class="postImageFloat scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/cfsuites.jpg" alt="Call for Suites image">

<p>On the top floor of Ballys are four penthouse suites, and we are calling for people or groups who are interested in renting them and throwing something cool for the hacking community. Here is the deal:</p>

<p>Come up with a cool concept, event, or party that will be open to all attendees from Thursday to Sunday and if you are selected DEF CON will release to you or your group one of the suites at a cost of $500 per night - so $2,000 for the con. They usually go for $1,500 to $2,000 per night.
You can read the whole announcement at:</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cfsuites.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cfsuites.html</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 01:11:36 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">06D6F7F0-8686-4BD0-BB66-8943DC49E6AD</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The DEF CON 23 Call for Music is Open!</title>
            <link>https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1A8w9C0P_vvqAjJ6S8SfKDzb1ZP2VQPR57Rhb5n4oxQI/viewform</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img class="postImageFloat scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/dj.jpg" alt="DJ turntables image">

<p>We’re looking for performers. If you’ve got a band, or some righteous DJ skills, or you are crazy good at Tuvan throat singing, we want to hear from you. DEF CON is a big event, and our rocking requirements are substantial. Even if you just want to spin some chilly beats for con-goers on a caffeine comedown - we want your application.</p>

<p>If you have the goods to rock the people, fill out this form. Get in the ring. Win DEF CON.</p>

<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1A8w9C0P_vvqAjJ6S8SfKDzb1ZP2VQPR57Rhb5n4oxQI/viewform">DEF CON 23 Call for Music</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 01:51:18 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">F6474195-7849-492D-9BBD-B9B57E5F91E3</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Today’s list: 5 Must-See Classics of Golden Age Film Noir</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-news.html#dc23noirfilms</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>To get you in the mood for DEF CON’s Noir theme, we offer some Film Noir knowledge and recommendations.</p>

<p>Noir is a slippery category, but it’s generally taken to mean films with a cynical worldview, moody, stylized cinematography and stories that turn on darker human impulses: lust, greed, vengeance.  They are stories of the desperate and the doomed, the outsiders who will never really belong to polite society.</p> 

<p>The golden age of film noir is the 1940s and 50s, but the genre left its mark all over popular culture and great noir (or neo-noir, if you’re not into the whole brevity thing) is still being made today.</p>

<a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0041G3YIY/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B0041G3YIY&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=XP6UTQEZUAFJH54F"><img class="postImageFloat15 scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/double-indemnity.jpg"></a>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0041G3YIY/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B0041G3YIY&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=XP6UTQEZUAFJH54F">Double Indemnity</a></strong>: Arguably the film that kicked off the genre. All the elements are present. The lighting is dramatic, the dialog is sharp and the plot turns on murder for easy money. Directed by the great Billy Wilder and written by detective fiction immortal Raymond Chandler. Double Indemnity is the heavyweight champ of golden age noir, with 7 Oscar Nominations.<br>
<br>
</p>

<a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B004S801YK/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B004S801YK&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=Z2OWZSAOIMUBKDQ3"><img class="postImageFloat15 scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/kiss-me-deadly.jpg"></a>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B004S801YK/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B004S801YK&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=Z2OWZSAOIMUBKDQ3">Kiss Me Deadly</a></strong>: Adapted from the Mickey Spillane novel of the same name. Starts with a disreputable private eye picking up a terrified hitchhiker escaping from a mental hospital wearing only a trench coat, and then things get weird. A Cold War parable with a breakneck plot, a mysterious box and as pitch-black an opinion of the human condition as you could put on screen in 1955.<br><br>
</p>

<a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00IP0L36C/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B00IP0L36C&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=UNSMXRLX3EI4SDMR"><img class="postImageFloat15 scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/out-of-the-past.jpg"></a>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00IP0L36C/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B00IP0L36C&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=UNSMXRLX3EI4SDMR">Out Of The Past</a></strong>: To create the mood of a good noir, you need actors with moodsetting skills - lurking, looming, smoking with intent. No one has ever been better at doing those things than Robert Mitchum. Pay close attention to his looming work in this film. 10/10 would cross the street to avoid. Bonus: You can check out Mitchum being extra foreboding in 'Night of the Hunter'.<br>
<br>
</p>


<a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/6305770328/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=6305770328&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=EAACBTQP45UZVXU2"><img class="postImageFloat15 scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/d-o-a.jpg"></a>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/6305770328/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=6305770328&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=EAACBTQP45UZVXU2">D.O.A</a></strong>: Some of the plot tricks in this movie might seem familiar, but only because directors borrow from it all the time. D.O.A. was pretty avant-garde in its time.</p>

<p>Our protagonist is dying - soon. He uses the remainder of his rapidly expiring time to find out who murdered him and see justice done. Lots of newer movies use the forced clock, the backwards storytelling, the inside-out murder mystery but very few of them do it any better.<br>
<br>
</p>

<a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0017122AM/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B0017122AM&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=4OC2KKNYPP5NQXS3"><img class="postImageFloat15 scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/touch-of-evil.jpg"></a>
<p><strong><a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0017122AM/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&creativeASIN=B0017122AM&linkCode=as2&tag=dc03f3-20&linkId=4OC2KKNYPP5NQXS3">Touch of Evil</a></strong>: The opening shot - a long, unbroken meander through the scene of our intrigue - is a clinic on mood-setting. Questionable makeup choices aside, this is the platonic ideal of what a dark melodrama should look like.</p> 

<p>Honorable mentions: The Killers. The Asphalt Jungle. The Big Sleep.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 14:23:25 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">716DE411-3B20-41E0-977B-97508474A554</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 23 Website is Now Live!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-index.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/dc-23-site.png" alt="Screen capture of DC23 website">
<p>You can tell it’s springtime in the Northern Hemisphere. The flowers begin to bud, the non-crow birds start to sing outside your window, and the new DEF CON website is launched. </p>

<p>The new website announces the theme of DC23 (The 23 Enigma: A Hacker Noir, for anyone just joining the party). As DEF CON 23 assumes its final form in the coming months, you’ll want to keep checking back. Bookmark that mug. Set it as your home screen. We’ll be filling the site in with speakers, events, contests, schedules and everything you need to make the most of your DEF CON experience. </p>

<p>August will be upon us faster than you’d think. Get excited, people.</p>

<p>And srsly, bookmark <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-index.html">the DC23 site</a>. </p>

]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 10:02:42 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">414EE0F5-F7CB-47A4-BD88-6579A0E30263</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Friends of Bill W Meetings at DEF CON 23!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-news.html#dc23aameet</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/dc-23-billw.jpg" alt="Poker chips with AA token image">

<p>Sin City is a lot to take in. Friends of Bill W. joining us for DEF CON 23 are invited to take a break from the Vegas of it all with meetings at noon and five p.m., Thursday, August 6 through Sunday, August 9. Your hosts will be Jeff Mc and Edward B. The location has yet to be determined, so keep an eye on this space and we’ll update as new information becomes available. </p>

<p>You can mail us any specific questions at info at defcon dot org and we’ll get what answers we can for you.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 16:55:26 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">09669CEC-96AB-49C2-99DC-96E8D28BFB66</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Go sign up for Capture the Flag at DEF CON 23!</title>
            <link>https://2015.legitbs.net/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/dc-23-ctf.jpg" alt="Capture the Flag DEF CON 23 image">

<p>CTF Season is in full swing - the final qualifying event is May 16-18. For those with the skills, the drive and the energy drink tolerance, glory awaits.</p>

<p>Screw your courage to the sticking place, step into the light and embrace destiny. Let the battle be joined!</p> 

<p>Also, register on the Legitimate Business Syndicate website. Then, embrace destiny.</p>

<p><a href="https://2015.legitbs.net/">https://2015.legitbs.net/</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 14:32:22 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4FA296D4-CC0B-45F6-8321-BC599E63F8BA</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Tamper Evident Village is back for DEF CON 23!</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests/dc23-villages/tamper-evident-village/220156-tamper-evident-village-returns</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/dc-23-tamper.jpg" alt="typewriter short story contest image">

<p>The fine folks from MFP are bringing back the village for everyone who wants to test their skills against modern tamper-evident technologies. Contests, workspaces, presentations and demos - the TE Village is kind has all kinds of stealthy fun for the sneakily inclined.
To learn more, check in on the Forum Thread:</p>
<p><a href="https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests/dc23-villages/tamper-evident-village/220156-tamper-evident-village-returns">https://forum.defcon.org/…/220156-tamper-evident-village-re…</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 12:03:15 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0B7A20DC-9D43-4A60-8984-5F2D1E36C45A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Reminder: DEF CON 23 Short Story Contest is Open!</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests/dc23-official-and-unofficial-contests/creative-writing-defcon-short-story-contest/219870-short-story-contest-2015-rules-and-themes</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/short-story-remind.jpg" alt="typewriter short story contest image">
 
<p>Friendly reminder to the writers in the DEF CON community:</p>
<p>The DEF CON Short Story Contest is OPEN. Like, right now.</p>
<p>The theme is 'The 23 Enigma - a Hacker Noir'. The contest closes June 1. Human badges are on the line. The rules are in the DEF CON Forums.</p>
<p><a href="https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests/dc23-official-and-unofficial-contests/creative-writing-defcon-short-story-contest/219870-short-story-contest-2015-rules-and-themes">https://forum.defcon.org/…/219870-short-story-contest-2015-…</a></p>
<p>Let's get those keys clickety-clacking, people.The drop-dead date is closer than you know.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 11:04:12 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">73B68706-A24B-4A6E-92EE-382D1D7E510F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The DEF CON Lawyer Meetup is back for 2015!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dc23lawyermeetup</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/lawyer.jpg" alt="lawyer meetup image">

<p>If you’re a lawyer (recently unfrozen or otherwise), a judge or a law student please make a note to join your host Jeff McNamara at 6pm on Friday, August 7th for a friendly get-together, followed by dinner/drinks and conversation. The location of the meet is still to be determined, but we’ll post as soon as the details are settled. If you’d like to help out with the event or have questions, contact jeff at jcmclaw dot com.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 14:13:08 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1B0C6B29-849C-4F24-A92E-20C9C6D78D5F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>303 Community DEF CON Party Fundraiser!</title>
            <link>http://www.booster.com/303community</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img class="postImageWide scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/303-shirt.jpg" alt="wall of sheep image">

<p><a href="http://www.booster.com/303community">303, perennial champions of DEF CON party-throwing, are having a fundraiser</a>. A fundraiser, amazingly enough, aimed at throwing an even more epic party at this year's DEF CON. Sounds good, right? </p>

<p>But there's more.<br>
In addition to supporting 303's patented brand of con-frolic, you can get something everyone needs: a classy black t-shirt with a geeky logo on it.</p>

<p>But that's not all!<br>
The 303 t-shirt features ultra-sexy artwork by the world-famous @eddietheyeti, creator of the 'Faces of DEF CON' series. </p>

<p>The combination is unbeatable. Good party karma and superfly, limited-edition threads. You know what to do.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 15:36:36 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C6C63E2D-6745-4C36-9E89-43748DD9587F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Wall of Sheep is Calling, They Want Your Papers!</title>
            <link>http://www.wallofsheep.com/pages/call-for-presentations-at-def-con-23</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/wos.jpg" alt="wall of sheep image">

<p>The WoS Packet Village returns for DEF CON 23 and they're looking for speakers. If you can cobble together a riveting 1-hour presentation on topics like network sniffing tools, or incident response, or Python programming for security practitioners, you can get selected to speak in the wildly popular Packet Village. Whether you're looking to dip your toe into speaking at security cons or you're a seasoned pro with an idea that fits perfectly into the Sheep demo, you owe it to yourself to check out this opportunity.</p>

<p>The full details are available at their site.</p> 

<p><a href="http://www.wallofsheep.com/pages/call-for-presentations-at-def-con-23">http://www.wallofsheep.com/pages/call-for-presentations-at-def-con-23</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 12:31:04 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0A16C70A-B39F-4968-8110-1D0D131463E1</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON CFP Privacy Policy, Now Live!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-cfp-privacy.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/post-images/dc-policy.jpg" alt="policy pages image"></figure>

<p>As you know, the DEF CON 23 Call for Papers is open. If you've ever been curious about how your sensitive research information is treated once we get it, who gets to see it, whether we put coffee mugs down on it - the <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-cfp-privacy.html">CFP Privacy Policy</a> we've added to the Policy Page has your answers.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 16:43:21 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C8D833CE-99CE-4ABF-A3B1-E41FC69EC2F2</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New! Black Badge Hall of Fame!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-black-badge.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/post-images/black-badge.jpg" alt="black badge image"></figure>

<p>The Black Badge is highest honor DEF CON can bestow. You have to do something awesome to win one, and if you manage that you get in to DEF CON free for the duration of your natural life. It is, in a word, ballerific. It also maxes out your charisma when worn with an ironic t-shirt.</p>

<p>We’re compiling a history of the winners, and we’ve put up a <a href="html/links/dc-black-badge.html">Black Badge Hall of Fame page</a> to get that process started.</p> 

<p>The thing is, we weren’t always so good at keeping records. Because we are a giant Vegas hacker party. It’s pretty likely we’ve left off some deserving names or missed an event or two that were eligible for a Black Badge. If you know something that got overlooked, or think we got something mixed up, please let us know. Drop us a line at info@defcon.org and we’ll look into it and fix what needs fixin’. </p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 02:09:55 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">CF8F7729-B860-4EF2-A2BC-D6D83978299A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Link Roundup: DEF CON 23</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/roundup.jpg" alt="policy image"></figure>

<p>More stuff returning for DEF CON 23!</p>

<p><a href="https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests/dc23-official-and-unofficial-contests/eff-sohopelessly-broken-eff-soho-router-hacking-aa">SoHopelessly Broken</a> - Last year's popular Small and Home Office Router hacking contest is back, with a twist!</p>

<p>Hair farmers, rejoice! The DEF CON beard and moustache contest is back as well. Your commitment to medieval grooming habits could finally pay off.</p>

<p>And from the DEF CON Forums:</p>
<p>The 'Be The Match Registry Drive' is going to be back for DEF CON 23. This gives you another chance to be a straight-up superhero by getting yourself on the list of potential marrow donors.</p>
<p>You need to be between the ages of 18 and 60, meet the health guidelines and be willing to donate to ANY patient in need. At the recruitment drive, you will fill out a consent form with contact information and a short medical evaluation. You will receive more information about what it means to be a donor and then you will swab the inside of your cheeks. Your tissue type will be listed in the Be The Match Registry until your 61st Birthday. If you are a match for someone in need, then you will be contacted for donation.</p>
<p>More info here:<br>
<a href="http://bethematch.org/about-us/how-we-help-patients/be-the-match-registry/">http://bethematch.org/about-us/how-we-help-patients/be-the-match-registry/</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 17:02:18 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FFDE62AE-EEBE-4267-B93C-030261DE5DD1</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New DEF CON Code of Conduct is Live!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-code-of-conduct.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/post-images/dc-policy.jpg" alt="policy image"></figure>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-code-of-conduct.html">DEF CON’s official Code of Conduct</a> is now live on the <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-policy.html">Policy Page</a>. If you’re planning to attend DEF CON, please take a minute to look it over. The rules haven’t changed, but now they’re in a handy written form for easy reference in moments of quiet reflection or in your hectic, on-the-go lifestyle. </p>

<p>You’ll be expected to hold yourself to the terms of the CoC at DEF CON, but you can take them with you anywhere. Feel free to practice the precepts contained in the DEF CON CoC in the non-DC situations of your choice, including but not limited to board meetings and LARP events.</p> 

<p>We appreciate you taking the time to familiarize yourselves with the code, and we leave you with a quote that we believe gets at the heart of what we’re trying to create here, from the collected wisdom of Theodore Logan and Bill S. Preston, Esquire.</p>

<p>‘Be excellent to each other.’</p>

]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 13:44:55 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E6503F1B-918E-4F8D-A539-9680C33C46E2</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Link Roundup: DEF CON 23</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#linkroundup4</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/roundup.png" alt="Link Roundup image"></figure>

<p>Lots of news today:</p>

<p>The Thursday track DC101 is back for DEF CON 23 and they have an open CFP! If you’ve got a good talk in you that can help people optimize their con experience or expand their general knowledge base, this might be a great opportunity to get your feet wet as a DEF CON speaker. You can find out what they’re looking for and <a href="http://www.defcon101.org/cfp.htm">apply on the dc101 page</a>.</p>

<p>For those of you of a literary disposition, you should know that the <a href="https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests/dc23-official-and-unofficial-contests/creative-writing-defcon-short-story-contest/219870-short-story-contest-2015-rules-and-themes">DEF CON Short Story contest is open</a> and accepting entries. The theme is “The 23 Enigma: A Hacker Noir”. You know, sleepless streets with a million blind alleys and rules that won’t stay put. Pleasures that can only be bought with pain. The pulsing digital cords that bind us together but keep us from getting too close. The spreading darkness the hackers see first, before the grazing genpop has any idea what’s coming.</p>

<p>And if you’re looking for puzzle challenges to hold you over until con, the good folks at Queercon have one or you <a href=" http://www.queercon.org/tracking-the-mark-protocol-challenge/">at this link</a>. Give it a shot and keep your puzzle muscle strong. DEF CON 23 will be here before you know it.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 15:17:13 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">75BC9173-EB90-4696-8702-CD89FB973EDD</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New FTC Contest, Robocalls: Humanity Strikes Back</title>
            <link>http://www.ftc.gov/news-events/contests/robocalls-humanity-strikes-back</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/post-images/robocalls.jpg" alt="FTC Contest, Robocalls: Humanity Stikes Back image"></figure>

<p>Rachel from cardholder services is back and there's a price on her head.</p>
<p>Fresh off the popular 'Zapping Rachel' contest at DC22, the FTC is returning to DEF CON this summer with a brand new contest and a big wad of prize money. Called 'Robocalls: Humanity Strikes Back', it challenges you to create a tool that allows mobile and land-line users to identify and block robocalls or deflect them to a honeypot for great justice.</p>
<p>The qualifiying round is open now and closes June 15. Qualifiers compete at DEF CON 23 for cash prizes, including $25,000 for the winner. You can find all the rules and regs on the contest website.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.ftc.gov/news-events/contests/robocalls-humanity-strikes-back">http://www.ftc.gov/news-events/contests/robocalls-humanity-strikes-back</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 15:16:09 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3EC87281-6EC8-42E9-9B25-8D57E47324B8</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Contests, Events, &amp;amp; Villages, Oh My!</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="images/defcon-main/post-images/c&e-ctf.jpg" alt="Policy image"></figure>

<p>We're a little past the halfway point between cons, but DEF CON 23 is already taking shape nicely! Cool stuff with intention to return for DC 23 includes:</p>

<p><strong>Contests:</strong><br>
Black Bag<br>
Crash and Compile<br>
Capture the Flag<br>
DEF CON Bots<br>
Darknet Project<br>
Scavenger Hunt<br>
Short Story Contest<br>
Schemaverse</p>

<p><strong>Events:</strong><br>
SkyTalks<br>
DEAF CON<br>
DEF CON Shoot<br>
Ham Radio Exam</p>

<p><strong>Villages:</strong>
Crypto/Privacy Village<br>
Hardware Hacking Village<br>
Lockpick Village<br>
Packet Hacking Village<br>
Tamper-Evident Village<br>
Wireless Village<br>
Social Engineering Village</p>

<p>And there's lots more to come.</p>

<p>In the coming days, we'll be highlighting different individual contests, events and villages in this space, so keep an eye out. If your favorite thing isn't yet on the confirmed list, you can keep tabs in the <a href="https://forum.defcon.org/forum/defcon/dc23-official-unofficial-parties-social-gatherings-events-contests">Contests &amp; Section of the DEF CON forums</a>. It's never too early to start planning how you're gonna get involved this year.
</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 15:50:35 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9808E1E6-AA86-431A-981F-E4CA30B992B3</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New Policy Page!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-policy.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/post-images/dc-policy.jpg" alt="Policy image"></figure>

<p>Today we’re launching a <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-policy.html">brand new policy page at defcon.org</a>, and we’d love for you to take a look at it, and only partly because of the emotional validation it will provide for our lawyers. There’s also a lot of useful information on the page for everyone who plans to visit our conference or our website. As of today, there are three documents up there:</p>

<p><strong>Privacy Policy</strong><br>
We make a real effort to protect whatever pieces of your identity pass into our hands, and we want you to have an understanding of what we can and can’t do to keep that data secure.</p>   

<p><strong>Transparency Report</strong><br>
It’s reasonable to wonder if sites you visit frequently have been served with a court order demanding logs and information. The transparency report is how you’ll know if it happens to DEF CON.</p>

<p><strong>Black Badge Policy</strong><br>
Wonder if that Black Badge on eBay will render you ‘uber’ at the next DEF CON? There are rules, and we wrote them down for you.</p>

<p>As other policies are finalized, we’ll update the policy page. If you need another reason to check it out, consider this: every time someone reads a privacy policy all the way through, a lawyer gets their wings. Or a lawyer does 1d4 of smoke damage. It’s one of those.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 15:49:06 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">53FD2C06-7F67-4F8B-BEE0-B4C49F528EE6</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Server Security Upgrades - DT's Blog</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/blogs/dark-tangent/219881-forum-security-upgrades-round-one</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/housekeeping.png" alt="Housekeeping image"></figure>

<p>After moving all of the DEF CON hardware (because the building was scheduled to be demolished – go figure), we started a pretty rigorous set of security upgrades.</p>
<p>HPKP support on the webservers? Check. DNSSEC support all around? Check.</p>
<p>In an effort to keep you informed about what we're up to, security-wise and to maybe inspire everyone to get up to date, DT has started a <a href="https://forum.defcon.org/blogs/dark-tangent/219881-forum-security-upgrades-round-one">blog on the DEF CON forums about the upgrade process</a>.</p>
<p>Check it out, and feel free to leave a comment!</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 14:23:54 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FA7F93C2-B172-49F0-BFB7-EE47CA983601</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 23 Crypto and Privacy Village CFP is Open!</title>
            <link>https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0xVlsTH0-EHREg0X0FBaklVRGc/view</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/post-images/crypto-privacy-cfp.png" alt="Crypto and Privacy village CFP Screen shot"></figure>

   	<p>Attention: The Crypto &amp; Privacy Village CFP for DEF CON 23 is live now!<br><br>
PS - Word on the street is there's even a puzzle in the CFP!<br>
<br>
<a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0xVlsTH0-EHREg0X0FBaklVRGc/view">Crypto And Privacy Village CFP</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 13:14:44 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">07A5D5F6-6611-407A-BBCA-4EED1D3F18CD</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DCG 719 Presents: 3D Printing</title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oUY8aQqCSRU</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/post-images/dc719-3d.jpg" alt="dcg 719 video screen cap"></a>

    	<p>DEF CON doesn’t just happen once a year in Las Vegas. It’s happening all around you, all the time. There are hundreds of DEF CON Groups all over the world that have regular meetings, put on talks and collaborate on projects of all kinds. You can be part of the one in your area, and if there isn’t one you can start one - it’s free and the information is available at <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-groups/dc-groups.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-groups/dc-groups.html</a>.</p>
        
<p>This week we’re sharing <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oUY8aQqCSRU">a talk on 3D printing given at DC719</a>, the DEF CON Group for the Colorado Springs area. Dana G. Neilson presents on the history and uses of 3D printing and shows how they made a pretty cool DEF CON ring as a handy example. More importantly he shows that what ever sector you work in or what ever you want to make, if you can visualize it, draw it and either CAD (Computer Aided Drafting) it or have someone else CAD it, then your ideas can become physical object. There are endless possibilities with this growing technology, become part of its growth and then share what you know.</p>

<p>If you’re in the Colorado Springs area and want to learn more about DC719, they’re online at <a href="http://www.dc719.net">dc719.net</a>. Introduce yourself.</p>
<p>If you’re part of a DC Group that has something they want shared by DEF CON, drop us a line at <strong>sleestak [at] def con dot org</strong>.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 20:03:08 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2A6AAFEB-BFF6-4AE6-BA7D-10C64341EF46</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New Speaker's Corner!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-speakerscorner.html#dt-p2p</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/speaker.jpg" alt="speaker"></figure>

    	<p>Sharing is our jam. We make an effort to get our product to everyone who can learn from it via all kinds of channels: YouTube, BitTorrent, direct download and even eMule. But security is also our jam. (We have multiple jams - deal with it.) So we’re putting a lot of thought into ways to make all that sharing more secure.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-speakerscorner.html#dt-p2p">This post from the Dark Tangent</a> is the first of several addressing the topic of more secure sharing, and it deals with BitTorrent.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 14:52:24 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">653418FA-7A8A-4B27-8EC2-2AEA56E5867B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The DEF CON 23 Call for Papers, and Social Engineering CFP are NOW OPEN!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cfp.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/dc-23-cfp-post.jpg" alt="DEF CON 23 CFP Graphic"></figure>
   
<p> It’s getting real, people. The <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cfp.html">DEF CON 23 Call for Papers</a> is now officially open! If you’ve got some good stuff to share, it’s time to start getting your pitch together. You’ve got until May 10th to submit, but don’t get too comfortable. May will be upon us faster than you probably think.</p>

<p>To learn the requirements for a DEF CON talk, take a look at the CFP form and get an idea of the suggested topics, we’ve put together a handy guide at <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cfp.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-23/dc-23-cfp.html</a>. Get yourself up to speed, get your forms filled out and get your proposal in front of our selection committee. This is going to be our biggest DEF CON yet, and there’s a lot of opportunities for speakers, both experienced and brand new. We’re hoping one of them is you.</p>

<p>As if that wasn’t enough CFP excitement, we’re also happy to announce that the Social Engineering Village CFP opens today! The requirements and submission form are online at <a href="http://www.social-engineer.org/sevillage-call-papers/">http://www.social-engineer.org/sevillage-call-papers/</a>. The SE Village is very popular and it’s going to be even bigger and more ambitious this year. </p>

<p>SE Village also has a bad-ass Capture the Flag contest happening. Check out the Rules and Registration page (<a href="http://www.social-engineer.org/ctf/def-con-23-sectf-rules-registration/">http://www.social-engineer.org/ctf/def-con-23-sectf-rules-registration/</a>). If you want to play, read the whole thing. For real. They’re very clear on this point.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2015 14:13:20 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">BAA0143C-F34E-4100-8662-3A98550014C0</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Resource Updates and a Call for Feedback.</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#cff-music</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/CFF.png" alt="Call for feedback image"></figure>

<p>We've added some links to the DEF CON website resource section: Some <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/book-list.html">movies to watch</a>, <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/links-o-rama.html">social media accounts to follow</a>, <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/links-o-rama.html">hacker culture sites</a> and <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/book-list.html">technical books</a> to get you on your way - today we're asking for music recommendations.</p> 

<p>What do you listen to when you're sitting in the dark, making faces at your monitor? We want to compile a playlist of tunes to code/learn/fall into an internet rabbit hole by. </p>

<p>Strong enough to keep you typing into the darkness, subtle enough to stay out of your way when the big thinking happens &mdash; Send your suggestions to <strong>sleestak at defcon dot org</strong>!</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 11:21:31 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A70C8D6B-8E8A-4379-8083-D6E6D8D08556</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New Speaker's Corner!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-speakerscorner.html#renda-emp</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/speakercorner/renda.jpg" alt="Paul Renda at DEF CON 17"></figure>

<p>The long-silent creature begins to stir! We have a new post in the Speaker’s Corner of the DEF CON website. It’s from DEF CON alum Paul Renda and it concerns future presentation ideas that involve Robots, AI and Tesla coils. Straight out of the DEF CON dream journal. You can read it here: <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-speakerscorner.html#renda-emp">https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-speakerscorner.html#renda-emp</a></p>

<p>If you’re a past DEF CON speaker who has something to share with the DEF CON community, please get in touch (<a href="https://twitter.com/_defcon_">@_defcon_</a> , <a href="https://www.facebook.com/defcon">Facebook.com/defcon</a>). We’re interested in what you’re thinking about and we’d love to help get the word out.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 14:26:48 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3C67298C-EA71-4E81-BD80-A2814B0DFC6D</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>More Upgrade News!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dcforumsupgrade</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/forums-upgrade.png" alt="DEF CON Youtube image"></figure>

<p>More upgrade news! We're rolling out a major upgrade to the forums next week. New coat of paint, improved functionality, general up-leveling across the board. But wait - there's more! As soon as we've sorted out the new setup, we'll be releasing a mobile app version for Android and iOS. Stay tuned!</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 22:18:47 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B65794A1-DD2B-4342-AAFF-1BFC300061BE</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22, now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/user/DEFCONConference</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-youtube.png" alt="DEF CON Youtube image"></figure>

<p>Good News, Everyone! The DEF CON YouTube channel now contains the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/DEFCONConference">full slate of presentations from DEF CON 22</a>! </p>

<p>Delivered on Thursday to help you get a jump start on your knowledge-binge weekend, we’ve got over 100 presentations ready to jump across your face-brain barrier. Don’t know where to start? We’ve included a handy playlist option so you can hit play once and not come up for air for a few days. For those who wish to watch in furtive silence so as not to arouse the pointy-headed boss, there are captions.</p>

<p>You might want to consider taking a personal day.</p>

<p>Please enjoy and spread the word. Share the videos with people you think can learn from them. Pass it on.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 15:20:37 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2A5FD961-6272-4B2D-BA81-872A5BE56CEB</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Server Move Completed</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#servermoved</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/housekeeping.png" alt="Housekeeping image"></figure>

<p>Thanks for bearing with us during the last week or so, as defcon.org was migrated to a new location! We are currently getting the forums and Media servers buttoned up, and moving on toward DEF CON 23. Look for the Call for Papers to open in the next week or two!</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 15:17:11 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">AF71632A-710F-4FAA-BCE5-368EBBBC73B6</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Server Move Approaching</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#servermove</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/housekeeping.png" alt="Housekeeping image"></figure>

<p>We’re moving to a new office in a few days, so please excuse any availability issues for the near future. We’re going to do our best to keep the site and the forums running smoothly through the whole transfer, but if you notice hiccups please know that we’ll be back to normal very soon.</p>

<p>In the meantime, if you need up-to-the minute news about what’s going on in the world of DEF CON, please visit us at <a href="https://www.facebook.com/defcon">Facebook.com/defcon</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/_defcon_">@_defcon_</a> on Twitter or our <a href="https://plus.google.com/u/0/109290251360103915496/">Google Plus</a> page.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 18:55:02 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">282D0389-82F0-4144-9879-B5DD01CAFA99</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Happy New Year from DEF CON!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#newyear2015</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/dc-new-year-2015.jpg" alt="New year image"></figure>

<p>DEF CON had a pretty great year, thanks to all of you. It takes a huge effort from so many people to create the kind of magical hacker summer camp that DEF CON has become, and we want to thank all of you for the parts you play:</p>

<p>
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;• The geniuses who create the talks and the geniuses who review and select them.<br><br>
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;• The mad zealots who dream up and carry out the contests and events.<br><br>
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;• The dedicated army of goons who descend upon a nondescript Vegas hotel every summer and turn it into a hacker utopia by sheer brute force and guile.<br><br>
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;• The attendees whose love, devotion and enthusiasm keeps this whole enterprise aloft.<br><br>
</p>

<p>DC22 had our biggest attendance ever.  So big that some of the villages are probably bigger than the first several DEF CONs. So big, in fact, that DEF CON 23 will be in two hotels. Imagine that!</p>

<p>We will be occupying both Bally’s and Paris for DEF CON 23. More space, bigger villages, shorter lines. Like always, we’re counting on DC’s volunteers and the community at large to fill all that new space with ideas and ingenuity. It’s the greatest thing about running this type of conference - no matter what new ideas we throw out there, the community never fails to push it further than we imagined.</p>

<p>Thanks to everyone who made 2014 so great, and let’s get amped for an epic 2015.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 21:52:36 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D3BA8C5E-8B18-4FF2-86E6-FFAF76802545</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Social Media Cleanup</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dcsmhousekeeping</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/housekeeping.png" alt="Housekeeping image"></figure>

<p>As part of our social media housekeeping for the new year, we're leaving LinkedIn. As much as we like the service, we couldn't help but feel that we weren't using it to its potential, and that we were doing more to harvest spam than to communicate with all of you.</p>

<p>If you're one of the people who connected with DEF CON on LinkedIn, you should know that we won't do anything hasty. We'll leave everything where it is through January 2015, to give everyone time to collect whatever they need from our LinkedIn presence.</p>

<p>More importantly, we hope that you'll check out our other social media options. We have an active presence on <a href="https://plus.google.com/u/0/109290251360103915496/">G+</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/defcon">Facebook</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/_defcon_">Twitter</a> and we're going to spend more time hanging out in <a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/defcon">r/defcon</a> in the days ahead as well.</p>

<p>We have big plans for DEF CON 23, and we want your input.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 12:42:19 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">CA8CE0F9-314B-475E-AC99-9BF8A100A93E</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Capture the Flag qualifying events announced!</title>
            <link>https://blog.legitbs.net/2014/12/announcing-def-con-ctf-qualifying.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/dc23-ctf.png" alt="CTF graphic"></figure>

<p>
Begun, the DC23 CTF has!</p>

<p>Legitimate Business Syndicate, the shadowy organization that provides the hustle and the muscle behind the DEF CON CTF tournament, has announced its list of qualifying contests for the 2015 showdown in Las Vegas.</p>

<p>If you have the team, the drive and the raw skills, it's time to start making plans. To pluck the flower of eternal glory from the Nevada desert, you must first prove yourself in the crucible of a qualifier.</p>

<p>Assemble. Register. Qualify. Prevail. The road to victory is now open.</p>

<p><a href="https://blog.legitbs.net/2014/12/announcing-def-con-ctf-qualifying.html">https://blog.legitbs.net/2014/12/announcing-def-con-ctf-qualifying.html</a>

</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 16:52:32 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B730E2C8-5200-4D9E-9AE1-3BAC3FF23CBF</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>More Video torrents from DEF CON 22!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dc22videoorslides</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-itunes-logo-video-sm.jpg" alt="DEF CON video archive image"></figure>

    	<p>We've got two more versions of the DC22 talks available for your torrenting pleasure. We've got <a href="html/torrent/DEF CON 22 slides.torrent">slide only video</a>, with the audio and slides uninterrupted by speaker face. We've also got <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 video.torrent">talking head video</a>, which is audio and speaker face uninterrupted by slides.</p>

<p>If either one of those is your preferred flavor, then your moment has arrived. As always, we ask only that you enjoy them and seed them so others can enjoy them as well.</p>

<p>It's us against the derp, people. Let's spread the knowledge.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 12:28:44 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FEA09DBC-BE14-4EA6-862D-D591C26A379C</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Video and Slides Torrent Update!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dc22videoandslidesupdate</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-itunes-logo-video-sm.jpg" alt="DEF CON torrent image"></figure>

    	<p>Torrent update: 12 of the talks were missing from the first DEF CON 22 video/slides torrent, due to some unicode mishaps in their file names. We've corrected the links - this updated torrent file will complete your collection. As always, enjoy and pass it on.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 video and slides.torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 video and slides.torrent</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 10:25:44 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A4909772-FA70-494F-8A0D-E0365C5748F1</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Audio Torrent is Live!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF%20CON%2022%20audio.torrent</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-itunes-logo-audio-sm.jpg" alt="DEF CON Call for Feedback image"></figure>

  	<p>Waiting for the DEF CON 22 audio-only torrent? Wait no more! Every talk in one juicy torrent. Slurp them, seed them and load them into the noise-producing device of your choice. Feel the commute flying by - embiggening your brain painlessly as you go! </p>

<p>Enjoy, and share the love.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 audio.torrent">DEF CON 22 audio torrent</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 13:20:27 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">EAC3135B-A347-4EFE-AC26-A294DE09A138</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Call for Feedback and Resources Updates!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dcfeedbackfiction</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/CFF.png" alt="DEF CON Call for Feedback image"></figure>

    	<p>What's your favorite recent (2000 and later) tech/hacker/geek fiction?</p>

<p>The update of the DEF CON resources section continues. This time we're looking for your favorites in the area of fiction. What tales of geekery and hackerdom have captured your attention in recent years? In our hemisphere, the onset of winter brings with it a craving for meaty tomes to sustain us in our long hibernation. Share your favorites with us! Send suggestions to sleestak [at] defcon ]dot[ org!</p>

<p>We've updated the site's '<a href="html/links/book-list.html">Resources/Book List</a>' and '<a href="html/links/links-o-rama.html">Resources/Links We Like</a>' with some of your suggestions, but if you have something to add to those lists, we're always listening. </p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 01:50:13 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">74136E7D-D37D-4F5E-AFE9-7086D40E1D30</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Video and Slides Torrent!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF%20CON%2022%20video%20and%20slides.torrent</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent-smiley.png" alt="DEF CON torrent image"></figure>

    	<p>Time to fire up your netslurpers - the <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 video and slides.torrent">DEF CON 22 video and slides are available</a> for your datasuction. All the speakers, all the slides, in convenient Torrent form. Please enjoy them, share them, and seed if you are able. There's a lot of good stuff in there - you might want to block off a couple of days if you're a binge watcher.</p>

<p>Prefer a lighter download? Audio-only torrent should be live tomorrow. By the end of the week we'll have the slide-only and talking-head only versions too, if that's your thing.</p> 

<p>The wait is over. Download 'em, seed 'em and spread the word.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 10:36:34 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">875A683A-6487-41B3-8299-6B7B1A56B5A8</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON Swag now on eBay!</title>
            <link>http://stores.ebay.com/defconcommunications</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/dc-ebay.jpg" alt="DEF CON eBay store image"></figure>

    	<p>We've launched an eBay store for DEF CON swag and collectibles. Right now, there's only three items, but we're stocking the e-shelves right now. Stay tuned!</p>

<p><a href="http://stores.ebay.com/defconcommunications">http://stores.ebay.com/defconcommunications</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 17:34:13 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6D4884BE-4F3C-4300-936E-D732E47CC3E6</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#happyturkey14</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/dc-turkey.png" alt="Happy Thanksgiving image"></figure>

    	<p>As you dig into the turkey, and enjoy the company of friends and family, we at DEF CON want you to know we’re thankful for you, the hacker community. You put so much into our conference , and make it something special! Happy Thanksgiving everyone!</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 11:47:34 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">36A83A4D-4291-457A-9B63-721ABD662BD7</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 23 Theme Announcement!</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=14096</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/dc23-theme.png" alt="DEF CON 23 Theme image"></figure>

We’re announcing the theme for DEF CON 23 early. Like, hella early. Right now early.<p>

<p>The theme will be ‘The 23 Enigma - a Hacker Noir’.  Fedoras and rain-slicked streets. Smoky back rooms and numbers that show up too often for coincidence.  While the good people of Everytown dream away the dark hours, the data wars rage without ceasing. Sleepless vigilantes fight for the users, though the users may never know. No matter. A bottle of the good stuff, a fast connection and the room to do a righteous night’s work, that’s enough. It’s gotta be. It’s all that’s left.</p>

<p>Hackers, start your imaginations.</p>

<p>The Dark Tangent’s announcement is here: <a href="https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=14096">https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=14096</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 17:00:25 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6DC7E70E-92FA-441A-92BE-97F60F5B59FE</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Upcoming DEF CON Groups Meetings!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dcgmeetings1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/dcg-logo-light.png" alt="Link roundup image"></figure>

    	<p>If you haven't gotten yourself involved in a DEF CON group, there's no time like the present to make some new friends, contribute to some cool projects, and generally help make the world a more hacker-friendly place. You can find information about DCGroups on the defcon forum, and in the <a href="html/defcon-groups/dc-groups.html">groups section on defcon.org</a>. Can't find one nearby? Start one!</p>

<p>Here's a short list of some of the US DCGroups meetings going on in the next few days:</p>

<p><strong>Wednesday, November 12</strong><br><br>
DC214 (Dallas/Fort Worth) 7pm at Lakewood's First and 10 - contact (<a href="http://www.dc214.org">dc214.org</a>)</p>

<p><strong>Thursday, November 13</strong><br><br>
DC412 (Pittsburgh) 7pm at SEI Building, Oakland PA (rsvp at <a href="http://www.meetup.com/Steel-City-InfoSec/events/">http://www.meetup.com/Steel-City-InfoSec/events/</a>)<br>
DC612 (Minneapolis) 6pm at Elsies Bar and Bowling Alley - event page (<a href="http://www.dc612.org">dc612.org</a>)</p>

<p><strong>Friday, November 14</strong><br><br>
DC719 (Colorado Springs) 7pm CTU Room 112 (<a href="http://www.dc719.net">dc719.net</a>)<br>
DC801 (Salt Lake City) 5pm at 801 Labs (<a href="http://www.dc801.org">dc801.org</a>)</p>

<p>DCG POCs - got something going on you don't see here? let us know!</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 13:44:05 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">F6A11C44-3004-421A-8C31-3A3ABE13AD3F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Link Roundup: Onymous Edition</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dclinkroundup3</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/roundup.png" alt="Link roundup image"></figure>

    	<p>Last week 'Operation Onymous' - a Law Enforcement sweep of Tor hidden services websites - netted about 400 takedowns and 17 arrests. </p>

<p>The Tor blog has a post summarizing what happened, offering suggestions and soliciting feedback. The operator of seized hidden service site Doxbin has released his logs in hopes of helping find how the network was compromised.</p> 

<p>For anyone looking for a discussion of the Tor network, what it can and cannot do and what users must do to maximize its effectiveness, we offer a talk from the Tor Project's Runa Sandvik from DEF CON 21.</p>

<p><a href="http://youtu.be/qWr5D2RoXoo">http://youtu.be/qWr5D2RoXoo</a><br><br>

<a href="https://blog.torproject.org/blog/thoughts-and-concerns-about-operation-onymous">https://blog.torproject.org/blog/thoughts-and-concerns-about-operation-onymous</a><br><br>

<a href="http://gizmodo.com/here-are-all-the-dark-net-markets-seized-in-operation-o-1656541553">http://gizmodo.com/here-are-all-the-dark-net-markets-seized-in-operation-o-1656541553</a><br><br>

<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operation_Onymous">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operation_Onymous</a><br><br>

<a href="http://www.wired.com/2014/11/operation-onymous-dark-web-arrests/">http://www.wired.com/2014/11/operation-onymous-dark-web-arrests/</a><br><br>

<a href="http://www.theregister.co.uk/2014/11/09/torpedod_dev_dumps_doxbin_files_after_police_raids/">http://www.theregister.co.uk/2014/11/09/torpedod_dev_dumps_doxbin_files_after_police_raids/</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 13:41:17 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C89F8E95-D33B-4491-80FD-9B0BFFF661B1</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Link Roundup: Assault on Mobile Privacy</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dclinkroundup2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/roundup.png" alt="Link roundup image"></figure>

    	<p>We've mentioned it before, but the news about government spying sort of drowns it out: the commercial entities tracking your digital footprints are just as determined to capture all of your data and use it against you.</p>

<p>This week's big corporate data collection story was about Verizon and the 'unkillable' 'perma-cookies' they've been injecting into their customer's web traffic. It's certainly more the rule than an isolated example of service providers getting all up in your KoolAid, but it's generated interest because Verizon is huge and they are going out of their way to circumvent privacy measures built into your mobile devices. </p>

<p>This link roundup is about the Verizon story, but it's also a general reminder of the hard work that many, many digital middlemen put into unraveling your privacy sweater for power and profit. It's also a reminder that we have to be loud about these intrusions if we want them to stop. Companies like Verizon are not going to voluntarily give up all that sweet data unless they know they're going to lose subscribers.</p>

<p>We close the roundup with a link to a turbo talk from DC 19 about one man's work toward unveiling the methods of some major corporate browser history snoops.</p>

<p><a href="http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com//2014/11/04/verizon-wireless-under-fire-for-ad-targeting-program/">http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com//2014/11/04/verizon-wireless-under-fire-for-ad-targeting-program/</a><br><br>

<a href="http://www.pcworld.com/article/2841793/twitters-mopub-ad-exchange-grabs-verizon-tracking-cookies-and-more-may-follow.html">http://www.pcworld.com/article/2841793/twitters-mopub-ad-exchange-grabs-verizon-tracking-cookies-and-more-may-follow.html</a><br><br>

<a href="http://www.slate.com/blogs/future_tense/2014/10/29/verizon_perma_cookie_mobile_carriers_are_officially_out_of_control.html">http://www.slate.com/blogs/future_tense/2014/10/29/verizon_perma_cookie_mobile_carriers_are_officially_out_of_control.html</a><br><br>

<a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/kashmirhill/2014/10/28/find-out-whether-this-privacy-killing-super-cookie-is-on-your-phone/">http://www.forbes.com/sites/kashmirhill/2014/10/28/find-out-whether-this-privacy-killing-super-cookie-is-on-your-phone/</a><br><br>

<a href="http://www.tomsguide.com/us/att-tracks-mobile-users,news-19848.html">http://www.tomsguide.com/us/att-tracks-mobile-users,news-19848.html</a><br><br>

<a href="http://youtu.be/BAdtXkus-Xc">http://youtu.be/BAdtXkus-Xc</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 13:16:10 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">78F36AE4-B231-4C33-BB27-A3363DD61E3F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Feedback Requested!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#booklistfeedback</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/CFF.png" alt="call for feedback image"></figure>

   	<p>We're updating the DEF CON website's resource recommendations, and we'd love some suggestions from you. We're starting with computer reference books. We want to know which ones you find yourself going back to, which ones changed the way you think. What computer reference book has been indispensable to you? Send your suggestions to <strong>sleestak at defcon dot org</strong>!</p>

<p>We'll be asking for lots of other types of recommendations in the coming weeks. </p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 13:13:39 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D84468C0-CB33-4F23-8D4A-0F111AC939E4</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Speaker's Corner!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-speakerscorner.html#callforspeakers</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/speaker.jpg" alt="speaker"></figure>

    	<p>We present to you, today’s featured DEF CON Speaker! The greatest ever! Ermahgerd look at it amplifry!
What a work horse! Never tires! All it’s bass…</p>

<p>Don’t like this? Do something about it. </p>

<p>If you’re a  DEF CON Speaker (past or present) and would like to write a post to become featured here, on the <a href="html/links/dc-speakerscorner.html">Speakers Corner section of defcon.org</a>, please send an email to Talks (at ) defcon (dot) org with your story.  Drop us a line, let us know what you’re working on or what you’d like to share. DEF CON Groups members and speakers that also includes you! What’s your group been up to these days? Topics can vary from discussions on latest buzzword, walkthroughs, attack & defense, bio hacking, tips for improving certain skills, opinions on the state of affairs, etc. The possibilities are endless, and we are looking for content that fits in the spirit of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Speakers'_Corner">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Speakers'_Corner</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 13:09:13 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1E1D418C-F6AC-4E85-82F5-8ED2BC9B4EFD</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Link Roundup: Crypto Wars Reloaded</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#mobileprivacy</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/golden-key-01.png" alt="Golden Key"></figure>

    	<p>In September, Apple and Google both announced that they were going to ship their new devices with encryption turned on by default.  </p> 

<p>This has caused some concern in the Law Enforcement community. James Comey, current Director of the FBI, went on 60 Minutes to urge manufacturers to reconsider. He believes that if the good guys don't have a 'golden key' to everyone's mobile device, the bad guys can 'go dark' and gain an advantage will lead to terror, child abduction and ‘threatens to take us all to a very, very dark place’.</p> 

<p>There are a lot of problems with this logic. For example:</p> 

<p>Evildoers always have the option of ‘going dark’, regardless of how much privacy we give up. </p>

<p>The 'golden key' isn't the only way for LE to get the data they want.</p>   

<p>Most importantly, it's not possible to create a back door that can be entered only by the pure of heart. If the righteous can squeeze in today, the sketchy will, inevitably, squeeze in tomorrow. Later today, most likely.</p>  

<p>Threatpost: <br>
<a href="https://threatpost.com/edward-snowden-and-the-death-of-nuance/103902">https://threatpost.com/edward-snowden-and-the-death-of-nuance/103902</a></p>

<p>Schneier on Security: <br>
<a href="https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2014/10/iphone_encrypti_1.html">https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2014/10/iphone_encrypti_1.html</a></p>

<p>NYT: <br>
<a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/17/us/politics/fbi-director-in-policy-speech-calls-dark-devices-hindrance-to-crime-solving.html?_r=0">http://www.nytimes.com/2014/10/17/us/politics/fbi-director-in-policy-speech-calls-dark-devices-hindrance-to-crime-solving.html?_r=0</a></p>

<p>Gizmodo: <br>
<a href="http://gizmodo.com/why-the-fbi-director-is-wrong-about-encryption-1648334901">http://gizmodo.com/why-the-fbi-director-is-wrong-about-encryption-1648334901</a></p>

<p>Just Security: <br>
<a href="http://justsecurity.org/16503/security-front-doors-vs-back-doors-distinction-difference/">http://justsecurity.org/16503/security-front-doors-vs-back-doors-distinction-difference/</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 12:33:26 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0AA5D5F3-B08C-4C04-A0F9-7EDBFDE45F7B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Materials Archive RSS is Live</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/podcast/defcon-22-materials.rss</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-itunes-logo-materials-sm.jpg" alt="Materials Archive artwork"></figure>

    	<p>Greetings, DEF CON community. Today, we bring you another update to our growing online archive for DEF CON 22 - all the <a href="podcast/defcon-22-materials.rss">links to the presentation materials, wrapped in a pretty little RSS bow</a> for your convenience. All the presentation slides, links to all the tools and extras, all by grabbing the link below. Perfect for every occasion, and excellent as a holiday gift for the hard-to-buy-for geeks in your life. Because we love you. Watch this space for more DC22 video soon. </p>
        
        <p><a href="podcast/defcon-22-materials.rss">DEF CON 22 Materials RSS</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2014 10:21:21 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6E09840A-0939-4AC0-84DD-8170A7D9CAC3</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Badge News</title>
            <link>http://forums.parallax.com/showthread.php/156782-DEFCON-22-Badge-Code-Schematics-and-Information-Here</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/badges.jpg" alt="Photo of DEF CON 22 badges"></Figure>

        <p>Sure, you love your DC22 badge. You love its sleek design and its powerful S guts. You swoon for its enigmatic symbols and breathtaking adaptability. But deep down, you worry that you could love it a little more if there was badge code available in C. </p>

<p>Worry no more. Instead, rejoice! <a href="http://forums.parallax.com/showthread.php/156782-DEFCON-22-Badge-Code-Schematics-and-Information-Here">Head over to the Parallax Forums and get to hacking that badge</a>, C-style. If you do something awesome, let us know.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 02:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0FA32AF2-E8B4-453C-85F7-EA9C0FE86F14</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hacker Jeopardy Night Two at DEF CON 22!</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/po9Cy0xaK9c</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/hj-video.jpg" alt="Screen Cap of Hacker Jeopardy video"></figure>

        <p>Because we love you, a midweek treat: enjoy the <a href="http://youtu.be/po9Cy0xaK9c">thrilling conclusion to DEF CON 22's Hacker Jeopardy</a> Competition. For those of you playing along at home, good luck. For those of you attempting to listen in a public space, be warned there is foul language shouted at weather-altering volume. Headphones suggested.</p>

<p>Enjoy, share, and begin assembling your team of heroes for DC23!</p>    ]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 03:09:24 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E055CB57-4598-48F1-A0ED-115D40422112</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Hacker Jeopardy Night One at DEF CON 22!</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/3_5rO3abWoM</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/hj-video.jpg" alt="Screen Cap of Hacker Jeopardy video"></figure>

        <p>For your enjoyment, we offer you Night One of our long-running hacker trivia gameshow '<a href="http://youtu.be/3_5rO3abWoM">Hacker Jeopardy</a>'. Match wits with our champions by playing along at home (beers optional). If you play along at work, remember the headphones. Salty language and lots of shouting.</p> 

<p>As always, enjoy and share. The exciting conclusion later this week.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 03:07:28 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ADC8BB76-A8E7-4CF0-A578-B9422D0936D0</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 23 Hotel Block Link is Now Live!</title>
            <link>https://resweb.passkey.com/go/SBDEF5</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-23/hotelinfografsquare.png" alt="DEF CON 22 hotel rate infographic"></figure>
        
        <p>The DEF CON rate is available at the following hotels:
Paris, Bally's, Ceasars Palace, Planet Hollywood, Flamingo and Quad.</p>

<p>To get in on this rate, you'll need to use this link.</p>

<p><a href="https://resweb.passkey.com/go/SBDEF5">https://resweb.passkey.com/go/SBDEF5</a></p>

<p>Do not worry if the form doesn't immediately show the discounted rate. To verify that you're getting our price you can mouse over the dates you've selected or begin the checkout process.</p> 

<p>If you prefer to use the telephone for this kind of thing, here's the list of participating hotels and the relevant Group Codes:</p>

<p><strong>Ballys</strong><br>
800-358-8777<br>
SBDEF5<br><br>
<strong>Paris</strong><br>
877-603-4389<br>
SPDEF5<br><br>
<strong>Caesars</strong><br>
866-227-5944<br>
SCDEF5<br><br>
<strong>Planet Hollywood</strong><br>
866-317-1829<br>
SMDEF5<br><br>
<strong>Flamingo</strong><br>
888-373-9855<br>
SFDCC5<br><br>
<strong>Quad/Linq</strong><br>
866-523-2781<br>
SQDEF5</p>

<p>We are excited about all the new space, and we hope you'll be able to join us.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 13:50:19 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0EF00D89-43C0-4DD9-B2EB-80EEAF703B16</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 Music is up!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF%20CON%2021%20music.torrent</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent-smiley.png" alt="Torrent logo"></figure>

        <p> Tired of listening to your mp3 collection? Looking for a way to spice up that ho-hum hard drive? When's the last time you and your music stash really... connected? </p>

<p>Take care of your ears. Hot DJ sets have been shown in clinical trials to help treat the symptoms of boredom, malaise and sickofmycollectionitis. Side effects may include stupid grin, periodic head nodding and uncontrolled shaking in the booty region. If symptoms persist for more than four hours you should probably drink some water.</p>

<p>Ask your doctor if <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 music.torrent">DEF CON 21 Music Torrent</a> is right for you.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 12:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B62EBC5E-3474-4786-BE67-653C2E413B19</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The DC22 torrent flood rolls on!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22torrents2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent-smiley.png" alt="Torrent logo"></figure>
        <p> First up for your next leech 'n seed, we have the video for all the Wireless Village talks. That's three days worth of talks about subjects like Software Defined Radio, Bluetooth and yes, the Pineapple. Get on it, and you could have a significantly higher Wi-Q by Monday.

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 wifi village talks.torrent"> Wifi Village Talks at DEF CON 22 - Torrent </a></p>

	</div>
</article>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2014 12:32:50 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9B5A5836-BF12-48B0-AD8D-1DE90BD0AAE5</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Capture the Flag Archive Updated!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-ctf.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/ctf-monument.jpg" alt="CTF Monument graphic"></figure>

<p>
<a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-ctf.html">We’ve updated the CTF page</a> on the DEF CON website. In addition to being the new permanent home for the torrent link to CTF packet capture Valhalla (170 gigs of that uncut raw), it’s also home to a small but hopefully growing number of walkthroughs and write-ups. As we get them in, we’ll put them on. </p>

<p>That’s what we are doing for you, for loving the CTF tournament. What you can do for us is seed, seed, seed and spread the word.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 16:01:47 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">771563F7-3EE1-4085-9EF0-0E685C11FC9A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Torrential Downpour!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22torrents1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent-smiley.png" alt="Torrent logo"></figure>

<p>Your half-full drives are vulnerable. The webs are just looming there, waiting to pump your memory full of bad music, dumb videos and pictures of other people’s unremarkable pets. Protect yourself. Fill up that dangerous unused space with DC-related goodness.</p> 

<p>So far, we’ve got six new and updated torrents up:</p>

<p><strong>DEF CON 22 Speaker Materials:</strong><br />
Updated Speaker Materials: <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 presentations.torrent">Torrent <img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent.png" alt="Torrent Icon" /></a></p>

<p><strong>DEF CON 22 Music:</strong><br>
Music CD: <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 music CD.torrent">Torrent <img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent.png" alt="Torrent Icon" /></a></p>

<p><strong>DEF CON 22 Badge:</strong><br>
Collection of files related to hacking the DEF CON 22 Badge: <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 badge hacking.torrent">Torrent <img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent.png" alt="Torrent Icon" /></a></p>

<p><strong>Collection of Hacker Documentaries hosted on defcon.org (Updated):</strong> <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON Hosted hacking related documentaries v3.torrent">Torrent <img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent.png" alt="Torrent Icon" /></a></p>

<p><strong>Collection DEF CON Hacking Conference Con CD/DVDs (Updated):</strong> <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON Conference CD DVD collection 2014.torrent">Torrent <img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent.png" alt="Torrent Icon" /></a></p>

<p><strong>Collection DEF CON Hacking Conference Programs (Updated):</strong> <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON conference programs collection 2014.torrent">Torrent <img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/torrent.png" alt="Torrent Icon" /></a></p>

<p>We’re going to be adding to that list in the coming days. Together, we will fight back the secret scourge of disk encruftment.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 23:13:57 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">730AC4E0-F8B4-40F0-B609-B5F05CB63152</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Closing Ceremonies!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22closing</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-closing.jpg" alt="Closing Ceremonies video screencap"></figure>

<p>
For today’s #defconflashbackfriday we’re going all the way back to August of 2014 and serving up the <a href="http://youtu.be/GR3pEVW6hZA">DEF CON 22 closing ceremonies</a>. So if you were at the show but didn’t make it to the end credits,or you haven’t been to a DEF CON and want to get an idea of the sheer scope of the event, this flashback is for you.</p>

<p>As always, enjoy it and pass it on.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 11:51:21 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E47732C1-CB55-4A66-ABD4-CBC4023AEE61</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Complete Packet Captures from DEF CON 22 CTF!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22ctfpcaps</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/ctf-monument.jpg" alt="CTF Monument graphic"></figure>

<p>Do we ever have a treat for you analytically inclined individuals. <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 22 ctf teams.torrent">The complete packet captures from the DEF CON 22 Capture the Flag competition</a> are now available for your leeching pleasure!</p>

<p>That’s right: 170 glorious gigabytes, packaged up in a handy torrent for your convenience! All of the traffic from the World Series of hacking contests, now yours to fold, spindle and mutilate to your heart’s content.</p> 

<p>Enjoy, share, and if you can, seed this data. Packet captures taste better when they’re shared.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2014 10:57:58 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9751B028-955C-471E-96C5-BDA5873BADE5</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Read All About It!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc_press/dc_press.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/press-graphic.png" alt="Old printing press with DEF CON smiley"></figure>

<p>Every year, we collect and share a sampling of the published reports from the press that covered DEF CON. It's interesting to see what gets the most interest, and it's gratifying to see that every year there are less stories about how scary hackers are and more stories about the incredible things hackers create and what we can learn from investigating the technology that surrounds us.</p>

<p>Transportation security, digital privacy, and the unexpected musings of eccentric AV software titans seemed to top the list in 2014. You can peruse the whole thing at your leisure on our <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc_press/dc_press.html">press archive page</a>.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 14:52:05 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C723C846-B1F6-4E02-B28F-AB6AC673DB68</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>For Early Release -  Dark Mail</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/TWzvXaxR6us?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBCdjbKFYjosh1s1EkaYdsQ</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/levison-watt.jpg" alt="Dark Mail screenshot"></figure>

    <p><a href="http://youtu.be/TWzvXaxR6us?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBCdjbKFYjosh1s1EkaYdsQ">Ladar Levison and Stephen Watt are working on the future of secure email</a>. For your Thursday, we offer you the peek into their work on DIME that they shared with us at DEF CON 22. It's a very interesting talk, with a lot of information and acronyms. There's a lot to learn about how email security is broken, and a lot of ideas about how it could be fixed in the future. </p>

<p>As always, pass it on. </p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 10:18:51 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0E8C4C61-E1A6-4FCF-B700-15BCF9D41CDB</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Video from Source of Knowledge!</title>
            <link>http://www.defcononline.com/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/tsok-dc22.jpg" alt="Sound of Knowledge screenshots"></figure>

<p>Maybe you weren’t able to attend the the hacker playground that was the 22nd DEF CON. Perhaps you did, and just didn't get to pick up all the bleeding edge research our speakers were throwing down. </p>

<p>Take heart, hacker brethren and sistren, our friends at the Source of Knowledge record it all, and you can purchase those presentations for frame by frame forensic dissection in HD video format! In fact, they also offer a streaming option for those that like to keep it online.</p>

<p>Check out all of the purchase options at <a href="http://www.defcononline.com/">defcononline.com</a>!</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2014 15:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A6AC9C9B-2EBB-4223-8F1C-A0F59AAD90B3</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Archive is Now Live!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-archives/dc-22-archive.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-archive.png" alt="Screen shot of DEF CON 22 Archive"></figure>

<p>Good news, everyone! <a href="html/links/dc-archives/dc-22-archive.html">The archive page for DEF CON 22</a> has opened for business. It feels like DC was only a couple of weeks ago, but you can already see the slides and extra materials from all the main-track talks.  We’ll eventually be adding audio and video as well, so keep an eye on this space. In the meantime, bum rush these Power Points to you heart’s content. </p>
<p>As always, pass it on.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 12:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A32017B7-8CDE-424B-8EF7-0607E62C64B4</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>For Early Release - The Internet of Fails</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/WHdU4LutBGU?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBCdjbKFYjosh1s1EkaYdsQ</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/lanier-stanislav.jpg" alt="Screen shot of Internet of Fails talk"></figure>

<p>Early Release! More video from DEF CON 22! This time it's a presentation from Zach Lanier and Mark Stanislav about the many ways the Internet of Things isn't ready for prime time, security-wise, and some insight into the work being done to make it safe to connect your various 'Things' to the IoT. Enjoy, think carefully about how much you need your SlapChop all up in the cloud, and share.

<a href="http://youtu.be/WHdU4LutBGU?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBCdjbKFYjosh1s1EkaYdsQ">http://youtu.be/WHdU4LutBGU?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBCdjbKFYjosh1s1EkaYdsQ</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 13:08:02 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">F261AAE3-B062-4B09-8F5F-8DD0C7FE7E3B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Contest Results Page - Now Live!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-contest-results.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dcresults.png" alt="contest results image"></figure>

<p>We had a lot of incredible contests at DEF CON 22. So many contests that they could have seceded and formed the People’s Republic of Contestia. So many, in fact, that the results are still coming in over a week later. To keep you informed, we’ve created a <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-contest-results.html">Contest Results Page on defcon.org</a>. Check out who won, find links to the contest websites for further information.</p> 

<p>If you don’t see your favorite contest, let us know <a href="https://twitter.com/_defcon_">@_defcon_</a> or contact the contest organizer and ask them to submit their results.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 02:50:19 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FFDE7B42-3BCE-46CE-BD2E-DF4BDE38A66F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>For Early Release - AM I Being Spied On?</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/Bc7WoDXhcjM?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBCdjbKFYjosh1s1EkaYdsQ</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/polstra.jpg" alt="screencap of polstra talk"></figure>

<p>The way I see it, Thursday is the Friday of the middle-week. So for your Thursday enjoyment, here's a talk fresh off the presses from DEF CON 22 - Dr. Phil Polstra speaking on low tech methods for detecting high-tech surveillance. Enjoy, take the info that works for you and pass it on. Share with everyone.

<a href="http://youtu.be/Bc7WoDXhcjM?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBCdjbKFYjosh1s1EkaYdsQ">http://youtu.be/Bc7WoDXhcjM?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBCdjbKFYjosh1s1EkaYdsQ</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 16:12:37 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">EBBEA177-77E4-4832-9502-2E551257E14B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ICS Village PCAPS from DEF CON 22!</title>
            <link>https://media.defcon.org/DEF%20CON%2022/DEF%20CON%2022%20ics%20village/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/icsvillage.jpg" alt="powerlines"></figure>

<p>More DEF CON 22 goodies for you - <a href="https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON 22/DEF CON 22 ics village/">the packet captures from the ICS Village</a> are available for you to download and dig through at your leisure. Also, if you have pics from the ICS Village, please share them with <a href="https://twitter.com/ICS_Village">@ICS_Village</a> on Twitter.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 16:09:59 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">35D7D7B0-88AC-4607-BFF8-CB3B2BD1DD12</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>For Early Release: War Kitteh</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/DMNSvHswljM</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/war-kitteh.jpg" alt="War Kitteh screen shot"></figure>

<p>One of the popular talks from DEF CON 22 - "Weaponizing Your Pets: The War Kitteh and the Denial of Service Dog" by Gene Bransfield. Enjoy, and share.
<a href="http://youtu.be/DMNSvHswljM">http://youtu.be/DMNSvHswljM</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2014 12:09:04 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">09A88FF8-225B-4219-BD99-1A3A8C9B3007</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Keep it going all year!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-groups/dc-groups.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/dcg-logo-light.png" alt="DC GROUPS logo"></figure>

<p>So you've been home from DEF CON for a week now - probably settled back into your normal routine. In the back of your mind, though, there's probably a little voice that wishes you could have DEF CON-style hacker camaraderie and learning opportunities all year long. </p>

<p>The good news is, you can. You can join a DC Group in your area. If there isn't a DC Group in your area, you can start one. The instructions for starting a group are at the link below, as well as a listing of the hundreds of groups that already exist around the world.</p>

<p>And when you get involved, be sure to keep in touch with us on social media. Let us know when you're meeting and we'll share it. Tape your presentations and we'll share those, too. Let's make this the fastest trip from one DEF CON to the next by keeping the ball rolling all year.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-groups/dc-groups.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-groups/dc-groups.html</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 03:13:54 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A0F9FC56-FDDF-48CC-9AC3-2E930A14B82B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 CTF Results Are In!</title>
            <link>https://legitbs.net/2014/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/ctf-visual.jpg" alt="attack visualization of CTF"></figure>

<p>Legitimate Business Syndicate has placed the final results of the DEF CON 22 CTF Finals on their website.There's scores, some shout-outs and even an explanation of their fancy radio badge and the cool contest visualization they debuted this year.</p>

<p>Congratulations to all won the right to participate, and extra respect to Plaid Parliament of Pwning, HITCON and Dragon Sector for taking 1st, 2nd and 3rd respectively.</p>

<p><a href="https://legitbs.net/2014/">https://legitbs.net/2014/</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 12:45:15 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1C8A99E1-DA84-4A69-AE25-83F4DA20D42A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CONversation with Major Malfunction - The RFIDler returns</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/omSi0t3BFAA?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBvhtb930C2lk2OZPTRsBfe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/major-DT.jpg" alt="LosT and DT Talking"></figure>

<p>What a difference a year makes. At DEF CON 21, Major Malfunction and Zac Franken created a Kickstarter for the RFIDler in a room at the Rio. At DEF CON 22, they returned with a mature and very impressive tool and even bigger plans for the future.</p>

<p><a href="http://youtu.be/omSi0t3BFAA?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBvhtb930C2lk2OZPTRsBfe">In this video, Major sits down with DT</a> to talk about the RFIDler project.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2014 15:27:14 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0175912C-A21F-4380-B7E0-39DFE573F47C</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CONversation with LosT, DEF CON's Mindbender-in-chief</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/whAjHh4LD9w</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/1o57-DT.jpg" alt="LosT and DT Talking"></figure>

<p>One of DEF CON's secret weapons is LosT, our resident Puzzle Master and Lord of the Badge. You can see his work all over DEF CON, from the insanely hackable badges to the secret codes and messages hidden all over the program and the venue.</p>

<p><a href="http://youtu.be/whAjHh4LD9w">Dark Tangent interviews him here</a> about all of his various DEF CON activities, his process and even gets a few hints dropped for next year's puzzles.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 13:27:41 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">17C3F9D2-8A0B-4E83-86E9-6D66896A85DE</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Here come the updates...</title>
            <link>http://potatohatsecurity.tumblr.com/post/94565729529/defcon-22-badge-challenge-walkthrough</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/circle.jpg" alt="DEF CON 22 floor circle"></figure>


<p>This was an amazing year, and we've got a lot to share about it. Tons of stuff coming down the wire very shortly. In the meantime, enjoy this VERY thorough walkthrough of the DEF CON Badge Challenge from Team PotatoSec (Warning: Spoiler alert for those still trying to solve):<br><br>

<a href="http://potatohatsecurity.tumblr.com/post/94565729529/defcon-22-badge-challenge-walkthrough">http://potatohatsecurity.tumblr.com/post/94565729529/defcon-22-badge-challenge-walkthrough</a></p>

]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 13:31:40 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ACBD26A8-E324-4536-A7BF-0214B81EB26D</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>News from the Front!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22update2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-web.jpg" alt="DEF CON 22 logo"></figure>

<p>The hackening is in full swing at DEF CON 22. The Rio is abuzz with all manner of high-octane geekery. If you're here, you're probably too busy leveling up to keep an eye on the press surrounding the event, so we bring you this mini-roundup of press links to see what the rest of the world is saying about us.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.wired.com/2014/08/defcon-2014-badges-revealed/">http://www.wired.com/2014/08/defcon-2014-badges-revealed/</a></p>

<p><a href="http://blogs.wsj.com/digits/2014/08/08/telsa-invites-hackers-for-a-spin/">http://blogs.wsj.com/digits/2014/08/08/telsa-invites-hackers-for-a-spin/</a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.scmagazine.com/defcon-traffic-control-systems-vulnerable-to-hacking/article/365416/">http://www.scmagazine.com/defcon-traffic-control-systems-vulnerable-to-hacking/article/365416/</a></p>

<p><a href="http://www.theregister.co.uk/2014/08/09/technology_and_market_forces_will_defeat_surveillance_society_claims_crypto_king/">http://www.theregister.co.uk/2014/08/09/technology_and_market_forces_will_defeat_surveillance_society_claims_crypto_king/</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 14:36:41 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">91F389CD-B299-446E-AFFB-2437CD7A146B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Quick Update Roundup!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22update1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-web.jpg" alt="DEF CON 22 logo"></figure>

<p>DEF CON is in full swing - so there’s a million things going on. Here’s a few recent news items to tide you over while we get the party set up.</p>

<p>If you’re one of those people that enjoys being entertained by entertaining entertainers, you’re going to want to check out our newly minted ‘Entertainment’ page. So much music - it’s like Coachella for people who people smart enough to test out of Coachella.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-entertainment.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-entertainment.html</a></p>

<p>For lawyers, judges and law students, there’s a Lawyer Meetup this year. DEF CON General Counsel and Chief Legal Raconteur Jeff McNamara invites all with a connection to the practice of law for a relaxed low-key meet up followed by a spirited trip to the Voodoo Lounge.</p>

<p>Don’t forget to stop by Track 3 at 9pm on Friday and Saturday for Movie Night with Dark Tangent. Friday we’re showing ‘The Internet’s Own Boy’ - a moving bio of internet hero Aaron Swartz. Director Brian Knappenberger and Aaron’s brother Noah will be in attendance for Q&A.  Saturday, we’re showing ‘The Signal’. Directed by Will Eubank (who will also be in attendance), ‘The Signal’ is a mind-bending new scifi film that starts with some hackers on the road to DEF CON.</p>

<p>A few pro tips: stay hydrated, remember to eat and sleep. Keep the program handy - it’s like the Galactic Encyclopedia of DEF CON. Bring extra socks. Make new friends. Hack 100% of the things.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 14:38:10 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B6A8041D-A5BF-4A0D-9816-0B17D17321A0</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>For the Kids: Rootz Asylum at DEF CON 22</title>
            <link>http://www.r00tz.org/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/rootz.jpg" alt="Alt text for image"></figure>

For the Kids: Rootz Asylum at DEF CON 22</h3></a>
		<p>Rootz Asylum (formerly DEF CON Kids) has a full schedule of goodness planned for your padawan hackers. Learning, competition, fellowship with other hackish youth. It's pretty great. Back-to-school will definitely be cooler for the kids who spent their summer vacation winning DEF CON.

<a href="http://www.r00tz.org/">http://www.r00tz.org</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 15:48:43 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">E9C415D7-3FF9-4AD8-957A-952DB2900C7A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Movie Night With Dark Tangent: ‘The Signal’</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22movie1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/thesignal.jpg" alt="Alt text for image"></figure>

		<p>The sci-fi mind bender ‘The Signal’ centers around hackers on a road trip to DEF CON, so we can be forgiven for being a little biased in its favor. But from that promising starting place, the escalating weirdness and suspense take the movie everywhere but where you might expect. We don’t want to spoil anything - you’re gonna thank us if you go in with a clean slate. We’re proud to have ‘The Signal’ for Saturday’s ‘Movie Night with the Dark Tangent’, and we’re prouder still to have director Will Eubank on hand for Q&A after the screening. The last reel will definitely make you want to talk to Mister Eubank. Make it a point to be there! <br /><em>Saturday the 9th at 21:00, Track 3</em></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 16:07:56 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FF9225ED-A8AA-4AA9-8D01-6679BC9C1273</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON MEDIA HARD DRIVE DUPING STATION!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22hddupe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/hddupe.jpg" alt="Hard drive dupe image"></figure>

<p>For even faster leeching pleasure of the conference media server we have invested in hard drive duplication towers, and next year DT plans to launch the Data Duplication Village.</p>

<p>Too busy to pick and choose what you want from the server and want it all?? This year we have three sets of 4TB drives that contain the same data as the media server, just split up and color coded. If you want to duplicate a particular drive you need to show up at the INFO BOOTH with your drives at the start of each day. First come First server. It will take about 8 hours to dupe a 4TB drive so a set will start in the morning and a set in the evening, to finish overnight. </p>

<p>There should be six 1:11 duplication towers (If they show up in time), with two for each drive color. That means we can dupe 66 drives at a time. Once enough people show up to fill a station the duplication process starts.</p>

<p>As of this writing it is sorted like this:<br><br>
BLUE Drive = Conference Archives 1 of 2, including DEF CON<br>
GREEN Drive = Conference Archives 2 of 2<br>
ORANGE Drive = Podcasts, Cryptome, 1.5T of the Hak5 archives, FOSS Operating Systems, all other content</p>

<p>There will be an updated list at the infobooth.</p> 

<p>Want in on it? Go buy some 4TB SATA II 7200 RPM drives <strong>(internal drives, not usb)</strong>. Buy three if you want to try for the complete collection this year. I'd do it in advance, I think the local Frys will sell out! Duping should start Thursday!</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 16:37:57 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">55810B26-3242-461D-AF2D-BE05C09A8AC8</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Music Announcement: THE ORB</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#music5</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/Orb_Web.jpg" alt="The Orb"></figure>

<p>You better have just done that spit-take. That's right. Electronica/Trip-Hop/IDM/dub music classics and pioneers: The Orb. They're here. They're kicking. And on the 3rd day of DEF CON (Saturday night/Sunday morning 00:00-01:00) their divine presence shall bless the glorious attendees who... attend their glorious and divine performance. Those who do not attend will be forsaken and cast into the dystopian landscape known as "the rest of Las Vegas." And so this event shall henceforth be written into the Dark Tangent's Book of DEF CON, Volume 22 - also referred to by some as "the conference program." So say we all. </p>
<p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CdMs7eqMvNg">The Orb - Little Fluffy Clouds</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RiIV45T_0_o">The Orb - Toxygene</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A-n4i0eX3aY">The Orb feat. Lee Scratch Perry - Fussball</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FbWqm7wzl-g">The Orb feat. Lee Scratch Perry - Soulman</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XwZL5_xCHxo">The Orb - A Huge Evergrowing Pulsating Brain That Rules From the Centre of the Ultraworld (Orbital Dance Mix)</a></li>
</ul></p>
<p><ul>Social links: <br/><br/>
<li><a href="http://the orb.com/">The Orb Official Site</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/TheOrb">The Orb's Facebook</a></li>
<li><a href="https://twitter.com/Orbinfo">The Orb's Twitter</a></li>
</ul></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 19:33:22 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">FA7CA5F6-9267-441C-B778-267ADD67F1AB</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Music Announcement: DJ Spooky (That Subliminal Kid) a.k.a. Paul D. Miller</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#music4</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/Spooky_Web.jpg" alt="DJ Spooky: That Subliminal Kid a.k.a. Paul D. Miller"></figure>

<p>A major announcement right here. We're bringing you the legendary DJ Spooky (That Subliminal Kid), a.k.a. Paul D. Miller. His CV runs deeper than the Mariana trench and is more Renaissance than the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles combined. Perhaps originally and best known for his artisinal music crafting (collaborating on projects with Meat Beat Manifest, Slayer, Chuck D.) and turntablism , he's become a university music professor (EGS, Switzerland), author (too much stuff to list), and an executive director of Origin Magazine. He's had his works featured in major museums like the Warhol, The Whitney, the Museum of Contemporary Art (Chicago), blahblahblahblah the pseudo-anonymous writer of this announcement could go ad infinitum. The point is, he's attained legendary-levels of awesome, and is coming to DEF CON to drop some hip-hop (perhaps with orchestral accompaniament) on Thursday Night in Track 1 (22:00-23:00)!</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jVCmHWzo8ug">DJ Spooky live on Engadget TV</a> (Oh right, he's recently been on an Antarctic expedition that was used for his latest album)</li>
<li><a href="http://itunes.com/app/djspooky">DJ Spooky's Music Mixing/DJing iPad/iPhone app</a> (... and is involved with app development)</li>
<li><a href="http://www.djspooky.com/imaginaryapp/">Spooky's upcoming book with MIT Press on apps</a> (... ... ...)</li>
<li>
</ul>
<p><ul>Social links: <br/><br/>
<li><a href="http://djspooky.com/">DJ Spooky / Paul D. Miller Official Site</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/djspooky">DJ Spooky's Facebook</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/subliminalspooky">DJ Spooky's YouTube</a></li>
</ul>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 14:50:16 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">589C14EC-AC21-4793-8547-88D4A8A920FD</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Music Announcement: Elite Force &amp; MC Frontalot!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#music3</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/EliteForce2_Web.jpg" alt="Elite Force image"></figure>

<p>A favorite from DEF CON XX (he dropped the killer set after The Crystal Method), we're bringing the near-mythical adrenaline-inducing Elite Force back for another sonic pummeling. Many of you may also recognize one of his prior projects, Lunatic Calm, which had music featured on films like The Matrix, Mortal Kombat: Annhilation, Drive, and tooons of others. We're extraordinarily excited to have Elite Force back, and we'll all need to be sure to keep our collective cholesterol levels in check to ensure we can survive his performance. Catch him Saturday night in track 1 (23:00-00:00)!</p>
<p><ul>Here. Take a gander at some choice recent Elite Force cuts:<br/><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iknGYZdifN8&list=UUP7BAdQEq-6euifl3sQdieA">Elite Force - Gamechanger</a> (WARNING: BASS MAY MELT FACES OFF)</li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4J5AdgFGggc">The Prodigy, Physical - Firestarter (Elite Force RVMPD)</a> (WARNING: SEE PREVIOUS WARNING)</li>
</ul></p>
<p><ul>Social links: <br/><br/>
<li><a href="http://www.eliteforcemusic.com/">Elite Force Official Site</a></li>
<li><a href="https://soundcloud.com/elite-force">Elite Force Soundcloud</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/djeliteforce">Elite Force Facebook</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/djeliteforce">Elite Force YouTube</a></li>
</ul></p>

 <figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/Frontalot_Web.jpg" alt="MC Frontalot image"></figure>

<p>Another throwback to DEF CON XX, we're bringing back one of the grandmasters of Nerdcore hip-hop, MC FRONTALOT. His prolific lyrical stylings have been proverbially known to knock socks off, so shoes (as always) are encouraged (we'll let sandals slide too). He's also the star of the acclaimed documentary <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1159722/">Nerdcore Rising</a>. Catch him Friday night in Track 1 (23:00-00:00), alongside other hard-hitters and partners in nerdcore-crime <a href="http://dualcoremusic.com">Dual Core</a> and <a href="http://www.ytcracker.com">ytcracker</a>!</p>
<p><ul>Gorge yourself on his flow and become a better person for it:<br/><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Op1i0B8-dJA">MC Frontalot - Nerd Life</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EMgsAD3D948">MC Frontalot - I'll Form the Head (feat. Dr. Awkward and ZeaLouS1)</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rjigODNy3jk">MC Frontalot - Zero Day (feat. Dual Core and ytcracker)</a></li>
</ul></p>
<p><ul>Social links: <br/><br/>
<li><a href="http://frontalot.com/">MC Frontalot Official Site</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/frontalot">MC Frontalot Facebook</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/tubist">MC Frontalot YouTube</a></li>
</ul></p>

</div>



</article>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 17:32:54 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">21C61A35-89F4-4B8C-97DC-C4BD7E595249</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON Entertainment Presents: Anamanaguchi!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#music2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/Anamana_Web.jpg" alt="Anamanguchi promo image"></figure>

<p>Today we announce eccentric retro electro video game chip-tune-inspired dance-rock that is purveyed by ANAMANAGUCHI. Not only is their music video game-inspired, their music actually HAS appeared on video games (like Rockband and Scott Pilgrim vs. The World). The real deal! Check &#39;em out at the Friday festivities in track 1. (set time: 00:00, Saturday AM)!</p>
<p>Also be sure to check out their totally rad and typically incredibly neon music videos:<p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6fdr-Fiv92c" target="_blank">Anamanaguchi - Endless Fantasy</a> (See pizza get launched into space!)</li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vc3JWo2iiGc" target="_blank">Anamanaguchi - Meow</a> (Neon black light explosion. More pizza.)</li>
</ul></p>
<p><ul>Social links: <br><br>
<li><a href="http://www.anamanaguchi.com" target="_blank">Anamanaguchi Official Site</a></li>
<li><a href="https://soundcloud.com/anamanaguchi" target="_blank">Anamanaguchi Soundcloud</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.facebook.com/anamanaguchi" target="_blank">Anamanaguchi Facebook</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/anamanaguchi" target="_blank">Anamanaguchi YouTube</a></li>
</ul>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 12:07:47 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">75048083-6F1A-49EB-A858-C7B8F8D39B3A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEFCON 22 Music Announcement: Zebbler Encanti Experience</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#music1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/zebbler.jpg" alt="Zebbler image"></figure>

<p>Do you remember the giant projection-mapped DEF CON exploded face? Or maybe the dragon installation? Or how about the DEF CON sign installation in the chillout lounge last year? These are the epic works of Zebbler's design team, who have also developed installations for the likes of Shpongle, EOTO, and a number of other class acts. But Zebbler doesn't just excel at design. He also excels, along with his comrade Encanti at music. Together, they form an incredible audiovisual duo that goes by Zebbler Encanti Experience, and they will be purveying this experience to you at DEF CON 22! Take delight in their glorious bassy weirdness at DEF CON's official Saturday evening event in track 1 (set time: 01:00, Sunday) !</p>

<p>Most of their music is free/pay-what-you-can too! Check it out:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://music.gravitasrecordings.com/album/freakquency"> Freakquency</a>, their latest album has just dropped</li>
<li><a href="http://music.gravitasrecordings.com/album/altered-projections">Altered Projections</a> is a killer recent remix release (free/pay-what-you-can)</li>
<li><a href="http://music.gravitasrecordings.com/album/psychic-projections">Psychic Projections</a> is their debut album (free/pay-what-you-can)</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2014 12:57:13 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">77A86086-14B7-4119-B063-1EA4A781480F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Calling All Accepted Speakers!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dccdmaterials</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/last-minute.jpg" alt="Last Minute graphic"></figure>
               
<p>Attention all accepted DEF CON speakers! The deadline for getting your materials in for inclusion on the conference CD is Tuesday, July 15. Pencils down. Pass your paper to Nikita. Thank you.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2014 12:54:48 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6A99BD55-F0BE-4BAA-9568-CB2733466062</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Capture the Packet Registration Open!</title>
            <link>https://www.capturethepacket.com/ctp_dc_signup.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/CTP_logo.jpg" alt="Capture the Packet logo"></figure>

<p>Registration is now open for those willing to push their Cyber Traffic Analysis skills to the limit, you can compete in the latest Cyber Analytics and Network Forensics Challenge. Now in its fifth year ! Capture the Packet has brought more APT’s, Trojans, Malware, Web and Red team attacks, network issues and sneaky covert channel coms to one event !  Do you know when important data is leaking out of your network and who is doing it - Can you handle the Advanced Persistent Threat ?  Can you spot that nasty bug your neighbors workstation contracted from visiting an infected website ?  Can you spot a networking configuration issue with routing, spanning tree, BGP or OSPF ? Do you know how to count your IPV6 lucky stars ?  Do you speak VOIP, MGCP or H323 ? We welcome everyone to try their hand at the most intense live network traffic analysis and forensic challenge, who knows you could be our next grand finals winner. You must bring your own laptop/computer to compete in this challenge, remember while this is not an attack game, it is a hostile network.</p>

 

<p>Details:</p>

<p>This year, the completion is handled in three Challenging phases:</p>

<p>Pre-Qualifying Rounds Start Thursday August 7th at 1:00pm and End Friday August 8th at 1:00pm<br>

Those that have the highest scores “overall” from all rounds combined, essentially 40 teams will move on to the qualifying rounds<br><br>

The Qualifying rounds are held starting Friday August 8th at 2:00pm and end on Saturday August 9th at 1:00pm<br>

The top 10 teams from the Qualifying rounds with the highest over-all move on to the finals held on Saturday at 6:00pm<br><br>

The Final round will consist of the top 10 scoring teams to survive the qualifying rounds,<br>

These 12 teams will compete in a two hour long finals competition to determine the winner</p>

 

<p>Register your team of two – at <a href="https://www.capturethepacket.com/ctp_dc_signup.html">https://www.capturethepacket.com/ctp_dc_signup.html</a>, or sign-up onsite.</p>

 

<p>Capture The Packet will be hosted in the “Packet Hacking Village” at the DEFCON Entrance Area !</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 13:37:50 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7A274C51-3E54-4277-A8F6-A2014EF826E8</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON’s First Google Hangout!</title>
            <link>https://plus.google.com/+DefconOrgplus/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/G-Plus-Hangouts.jpg" alt="G+ Hangouts Logo"></figure>
<p>We’re trying something new. Friday, June 27th at 11am Pacific Time, we’re hosting our first Google Hangout on Air. The guest is Jennifer Granick, DEF CON CFP Review Board member, preeminent hacker defense lawyer and Director of Civil Liberties for the Center for Internet and Society at Stanford Law School. The subject is <a href="http://www.wired.com/2014/06/davis-undermines-metadata/">her recent article for Wired</a> regarding the verdict in United States v. Davis and what it could mean for the future of mass surveillance.</p> 

<p>If you’ve got good questions about the intersection of law and ‘metadata’ collection, either leave them here in the comments or ask them live at the Hangout tomorrow.</p>

<p>If you’re not following us on Google Plus, the link is here:</p>

<p><a href="https://plus.google.com/+DefconOrgplus/">https://plus.google.com/+DefconOrgplus/</a></p>

<p>Join us, and as always, spread the word.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 13:09:55 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">08B84705-678C-4365-B32F-F00F44E87F62</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 CFP Review Board Revealed!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp-review-board.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/mic-drop.jpg" alt="Hand dropping mic"></figure>

<p>‘This talk is amazing!’ You say this to yourself (inside voices) while watching someone awesome say and demonstrate awesome things. ‘How does DEF CON consistently pick so many great talks? They must have a team of borderline superheroes slogging through hundreds and hundreds of proposals for months! Who could those paragons of determination and insight BE, exactly? How could I learn their handles and perhaps show my appreciation by buying them many beers?’

</p>

<p>Here’s an answer key to these questions you’re asking yourself:<br><br>
 
1.)This talk probably is amazing. Not really a question.<br>
2.)Lots of caffeine and eyestrain. Also dedication and love.<br>
3.)They do have a team of borderline superheroes, and there is no DEF CON without them. <br>
4.)They are known as the DEF CON CFP Review Board.</p>

<p>You can check out <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp-review-board.html">their page here</a>. And maybe show them some love.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 13:08:09 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">598EDDFD-050C-4450-A0B7-888F9C506E6B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Last round of DEF CON 22 Talks are Live!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#speakers5</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/mic-drop.jpg" alt="Hand Dropping microphone"></figure>

<p>This is it. The speaker list for DEF CON 22 is now locked and complete.  This means two things: DEF CON is really almost here, and we are now hard at work creating the Tracks and the Schedule (watch this space, buckaroos).  We're very proud of the lineup we've assembled, and we think you will find a lot of good stuff to choose from. Whether you're coming to Vegas or not, we'd love it if you'd take some time to check out the speaker list and give us some feedback  about what talks have you the most excited.</p>

<p>55 days, people. Get psyched!</p>
                    
<p><h4>New for DC101</h4>
<hr>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#PanelDiversity">Panel - Diversity in Information Security</a></strong><br>
 
Jennifer Imhoff-Dousharm, Sandy “Mouse” Clark, Kristin Paget, Jolly, Vyrus, and Scott Martin</p>

<h4>New Presentations</h4>
<hr>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Corman">The Cavalry Year[0] &amp; a Path Forward for Public Safety</a></strong><br>
Joshua Corman and Nicholas J Percoco</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Graham">Mass Scanning the Internet: Tips, Tricks, Results</a></strong><br>
Robert Graham, Paul McMillan, and Dan Tentler</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Heres">Hack All The Things: 20 Devices in 45 Minutes</a></strong><br>
CJ Heres, Amir Etemadieh, Khoa Hoang, and Mike Baker</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Hunt">Raspberry MoCA - A recipe for compromise</a></strong><br>
Andrew Hunt</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Lamb">Home Insecurity: No alarms, False alarms, and SIGINT</a></strong><br>
Logan Lamb</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Levison">Dark Mail</a></strong><br>
Ladar Levison and Stephen Watt</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#McMillan">Attacking the Internet of Things using Time</a></strong><br>
Paul McMillan</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Menerick">Open Source Fairy Dust</a></strong><br>
John Menerick</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Moneger">Generating ROP payloads from numbers</a></strong><br>
Alexandre Moneger</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#PanelEFF">Panel: Ask the EFF: The Year in Digital Civil Liberties</a></strong><br>
Kurt Opsahl, Nate Cardozo, Mark Jaycox, Yan Zhu, and Eva Galperin</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#PanelSurveillance">Panel - Surveillance on the Silver Screen- Fact or Fiction?</a></strong><br>
Nicole Ozer, Kevin Bankston, and Timothy Edgar</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Pinto">Measuring the IQ of your Threat Intelligence feeds</a></strong><br>
Alex Pinto and Kyle Maxwell</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Pinto2">Secure Because Math: A Deep Dive On Machine Learning-Based Monitoring</a></strong><br>
Alex Pinto</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Rowley">Detecting and Defending Against a Surveillance State</a></strong><br>      
Robert Rowley</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Smith">Advanced Red Teaming: All Your Badges Are Belong To Us</a></strong><br>
Eric Smith and Josh Perrymon</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Stanislav">The Internet of Fails: Where IoT Has Gone Wrong and How We're Making It Right</a></strong><br>
Mark Stanislav and Zach Lanier</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Vixie">Domain Name Problems and Solutions</a></strong><br>
Dr. Paul Vixie</p>

 </div>
 </article>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 12:23:08 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">F77A3C34-395C-43DC-BFD1-D9BBAB918E7A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON Secret Media Server Project Revealed!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22sekretserver</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/sooper-sekret.png" alt="ascii DEF CON Logo">

<p><strong>RED ALERT TOP SECRET WIKI LEAK SN0DEN LEAK GAMMA GAMMA ZF0 P0SSE DOC DROPPER</strong></p>

<p>The previously sooper seekret media.defcon.org server project has leaked out on the twitter and the face book. No use hiding behind our press secretary any longer, It's better to just admit it and let everyone make up their own minds.</p>

<p><strong>WHAT LEAKED?</strong> The Dark Tangent is collecting as much open source security conference footage, training materials, podcasts, white papers, videos, and anything else haxors may be interested in. He plans to make it all available at DEF CON 22 in August and let anyone download it, or even direct HD copy it.</p>

<p><strong>WHO LEAKED THIS SECRET PROJECT?</strong> The Dark Tangent. Oops.</p>

<p><strong>WHAT NOW?</strong> A huge burden has been lifted off of DT and he no longer has to live two lives. He can now focus on getting as much content as possible from the community.</p>

<p>That's where you come in.</p>

<p><strong>HOW CAN I HELP?</strong><br>
Send links to content you think everyone should have access to that is related to the hacking and infosec scene somehow. It can be an rss podcast, a .torrent of academic journals, and ftp link to text files, a web site to mirror full of source code, an svn operating system repository, a YouTube channel, whatever!</p>

<p>Send your links in an email to dtangent@defcon.org, or tweet them to
@thedarktangent and he will start the leeching.</p>

<p><strong>HOW DO I GET MY HANDS ON THE DATA?</strong><br>
At DEF CON 22 you will be able to get to the gigs in a couple different
ways. The con Wi-Fi network (at 802.11g speeds), through wired switches on 1 gig links in different areas, or by bringing your own 4TB SATAII or III hard drive(s).</p>

<p>We will have HD duplicators running all con copying drives for people who just want to drop off a drive and pick it up later.</p>

<p>Please help out with links, and we'll see you at con!</p>

 </div>
 </article>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 13:03:38 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">28F0E74E-9823-4586-AE42-9AC8A7F9CE5E</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Big 'Ol Batch of Talks!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#speakers4</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/mic-drop.jpg" alt="Hand Dropping microphone"></figure>
                   
<p>It’s getting pretty real, people. The speaker selection process is almost complete, the party and event planning is in full swing - DEF CON 22 is just a little over two months away!</p>

<p>To celebrate, another round of speaker announcements. Twenty-five more abstracts to help you create your DEF CON battle plan. We anticipate one more round of announcements before the roster is locked, but by now you should have a pretty good idea how much good stuff we have on tap. </p>

<h4>DEF CON 101 Presentations</h4>
<hr>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Bugher">Detecting Bluetooth Surveillance Systems</a></strong><br>
Grant Bugher</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Crenshaw">Dropping Docs on Darknets: How People Got Caught </a></strong><br>
Adrian Crenshaw</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Kelley">Is This Your Pipe? Hijacking the Build Pipeline.</a></strong><br>
Kyle Kelley and Greg Anderson</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Littlebury">Home Automation and Defensive Security Measures</a></strong><br>
Chris Littlebury</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#McGrew">Instrumenting Point-of-Sale Malware: A Case Study in Communicating Malware Analysis More Effectively</a></strong><br>
Wesley McGrew</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Strazzere">Android Hacker Protection Level 0 </a></strong><br>
Tim Strazzere and Jon Sawyer</p>


<h4>Presentations</h4>
<hr>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Bursztein">I am a legend: Hacking Hearthstone with machine learning</a></strong><br>
Elie Bursztein and Celine Bursztein</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Cerrudo">Hacking US (and UK, Australia, France, etc.) traffic control systems</a></strong><br>
Cesar Cerrudo</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Datko">NSA Playset: DIY WAGONBED Hardware Implant over I2C</a></strong><br>
Josh Datko and Teddy Reed</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Free">Check Your Fingerprints: Cloning the Strong Set</a></strong><br>
Free and Lachesis</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Gaivoronski">Shellcodes for ARM: Your Pills Don't Work on Me, x86</a></strong><br>
Svetlana Gaivoronski and Ivan Petrov</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Gorenc">Blowing up the Celly - Building Your Own SMS/MMS Fuzzer</a></strong><br>
Brian Gorenc and Matt Molinyawe</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Grand">Deconstructing the Circuit Board Sandwich: Effective Techniques for PCB Reverse Engineering</a></strong><br>
Joe Grand (Kingpin)</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Lackey2">Panel: Ephemeral Communications: Why and How?</a></strong><br>
Ryan Lackey, Jon Callas, and Elissa Shevinsky</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Leder">NinjaTV - Increasing Your Smart TV’s IQ Without Bricking It</a></strong><br>
Felix Leder</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Mahjoub">Catching Malware En Masse: DNS and IP Style</a></strong><br>
Dhia Mahjoub, Thibault Reuille, and Andree Toonk</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Major">Old Skewl Hacking: Porn Free!</a></strong><br>
Major Malfunction</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Miller">A Survey of Remote Automotive Attack Surfaces</a></strong><br>
Charlie Miller and Chris Valasek</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Molina">Learn how to control every room at a luxury hotel remotely: the dangers of insecure home automation </a></strong><br>
Jesus Molina</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Sapozhnikov">Acquire current user hashes without admin privileges</a></strong><br>
Anton Sapozhnikov</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Vedaa">Impostor &mdash; Polluting Tor Metadata</a></strong><br>
Charlie Vedaa and Mike Larsen</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#DWhite">Manna from Heaven: Improving the state of wireless rogue AP attacks</a></strong><br>
Dominic White and Ian de Villiers</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#KWhite">The Open Crypto Audit Project</a></strong><br>
Kenneth White and Matthew Green</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Wilkinson">Practical Aerial Hacking & Surveillance</a></strong><br>
Glenn Wilkinson</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Zoz">Don't Fuck It Up!</a></strong><br>
Zoz</p>

 </div>
 </article>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 14:57:16 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2CBA3435-D977-42EB-93EE-4E8DCF1C78E7</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DARPA announces its 2-year Cyber Grand Challenge, Final Tournament at DEF CON 24</title>
            <link>http://www.darpa.mil/cybergrandchallenge/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/darpacgc.png" alt="DARPA Cyber Grand Challenge Logo"></figure>

<p>The Cyber Grand Challenge asks some simple questions - can you create a fully-automated system to detect, thwart and mitigate network attacks? Can you build one so effective that it can win an all-computer tournament without human intervention? Would you like 2 million dollars?</p>

<p>If you have a great proposal but lack the funds for a 2-year competition, you can pitch DARPA for funding - they’re already backing seven of the registered teams. Teams that survive the quals in June 2015 are eligible to compete in the final tournament at DEF CON in 2016. Grand prize is $2 million dollars. </p>

<p>Competitors will need a dizzying array of skills and an encyclopedic understanding of every form of network kung-fu. They will also need a pretty serious amount of free time, but the winner gets a nice check and an answer to the question of what to put first on a resum&eacute;.</p> 

<p>We believe that such a team must exist in the DEF CON family. If you think you’re up to the challenge, more information awaits you at the DARPA CGC page.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.darpa.mil/cybergrandchallenge/">http://www.darpa.mil/cybergrandchallenge/</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 12:40:01 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8477B91C-5A7E-4821-81A9-A25722FF8663</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Vote for your favorite short story!</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/forumdisplay.php?f=796</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/ssc.png" alt="Short story contest Logo"></figure>
                
<p>The DEF CON 22 Short Story Contest is now closed. Time for you to head over to the forums and vote for the People's Choice Awards. You're the people. Get in there. Be somebody.</p>

<p><a href="https://forum.defcon.org/forumdisplay.php?f=796">https://forum.defcon.org/forumdisplay.php?f=796</a></p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:52:30 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">213B110E-A8F5-471B-8D7C-2242412A3FC9</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Enormous Speaker Update! First DC101 Talks Revealed!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#speakers4</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/mic-drop.jpg" alt="Hand dropping Microphone with DC22 Logo">

<p>Hot off the presses - more speaker selections. Several of them are for the DEF CON 101 Track, newly expanded for DC 22 and running all the way through the con. The rest of the presentations listed here fall into the other tracks, and if we do say so ourselves, this is shaping up to be quite the year, hackwise. You’re definitely going to want to make sure you have a seat for some of these. The titles alone should tell you we’re coming correct in 2014.</p>

<h3>New Presentations</h3>
<hr>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Bruno">The Simple Route to Backbone Routers</a><br>
Luca "kaeso" Bruno and Mariano "emdel" Graziano</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Bulygin">Summary of Attacks Against BIOS and Secure Boot</a><br>
Yuriy Bulygin, Oleksandr Bazhaniuk, Andrew Furtak, and John Loucaides</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Eijah">Saving Cyberspace by Reinventing File Sharing</a><br>
Eijah</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Kaminsky">Secure Random By Default</a><br>
Dan Kaminsky</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Lackey">Masquerade: How a Helpful Man-in-the-Middle Can Help You Evade Monitoring. </a><br>
Ryan Lackey and Marc Rogers</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Erven">Just What The Doctor Ordered?</a><br>
Scott Erven and Shawn Merdinger</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Pierce">NSA Playset : GSM Sniffing</a><br>
Pierce and Loki</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Self">Don't DDoS Me Bro: Practical DDoS Defense</a><br>
Blake Self and Shawn "cisc0ninja" Burrell</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Street">"Around the world in 80 cons” - A Perspective</a><br>
Jayson E. Street</strong></p>




<h3>DEF CON 101 Presentations!</h3>
<hr>
<h4>Now running Thurdsay through Sunday!</h4>
<p>The DEF CON 101 track is a series of talks aimed at attendees who are not yet internationally-recognized infosec experts. This is not the n00b track. But if you're interested and engaged in the hacker community, these sessions are right up your alley. From Sysadmins & NOC Jockeys to College Students & IT Professionals, everyone exploring the world of Information Security can expect to feel welcome, not intimidated. We have grouped the sessions by interest area, so you're not spending all day bouncing between talks.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#DC101">DEF CON 101 - The Talk</a><br>
HighWiz, Lockheed, Pyr0, Roamer, and LosT</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#AlxRogan">Protecting SCADA From the Ground Up</a><br>
AlxRogan</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Dameff">Hacking 911: Adventures in Disruption, Destruction, and Death</a><br>
Christian “quaddi” Dameff, Jeff “r3plicant” Tully, and Peter Hefley</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Denaro">How to Disclose an Exploit Without Getting in Trouble</a><br>
Jim Denaro and Tod Beardsley</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#FitzPatrick">NSA Playset: PCIe</a><br>
Joe FitzPatrick, Miles Crabill, and Dean Pierce</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Gareau">Oh Bother, Cruising The Internet With Your Honeys, Creating Honeynets For Tracking Criminal Organizations </a><br>
Terrence Gareau and Mike Thompson</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Anch">The Monkey in the Middle: A pentesters guide to playing in traffic.</a><br>
Anch</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Kazanciyan">Investigating PowerShell Attacks</a><br>
Ryan Kazanciyan and Matt Hastings</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Kouns">Screw Becoming A Pentester - When I Grow Up I Want To Be A Bug Bounty Hunter!</a><br>
Jake Kouns and Carsten Eiram</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#McDonald">Meddle: Framework for Piggy-back Fuzzing and Tool Development</a><br>
Geoff McDonald</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Medic">One Man Shop: Building an Effective Security Program All By Yourself</a><br>
Medic</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#RMellendick">Rf Penetration Testing, Your Air Stinks</a><br>
RMellendick and DaKahuna</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Metacortex">Touring the Darkside of the Internet. An introduction to Tor, Darknets, and Bitcoin. </a><br>
Metacortex and Grifter</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Michael">USB for All!</a><br>
Jesse Michael and Mickey Shkatov</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Morris">ShareEnum: We Wrapped Samba So You Don’t Have To</a><br>
Lucas Morris and Michael McAtee</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Nemus">An Introduction to Back Dooring Operating Systems for Fun and Trolling</a><br>
Nemus</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Wiseacre">Standing Up an Effective Penetration Testing Team</a><br>
Wiseacre</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#PTzero">Data Protection 101 - Successes, Fails, and Fixes</a><br>
PTzero</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#PushPin">Anatomy of a Pentest; Poppin' Boxes like a Pro</a><br>
PushPin</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Wirth">Practical Foxhunting 101</a><br>
Adam Wirth (SimonJ)</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Soghoian">Blinding The Surveillance State </a><br>
Christopher Soghoian</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Valtman2">Bug Bounty Programs Evolution</a><br>
Nir Valtman</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Wyde">Client-Side HTTP Cookie Security: Attack and Defense</a><br>
David Wyde</strong></p></p>

</div>

</article>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 13:41:34 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">77F7050F-DCED-46BC-B468-6EFBA16E9F3F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 CTF Quals Roundup!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#ctfqualsroundup</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/sunset-ctf.png" alt="CTF sunset"></figure>
                    
<p>The DEF CON 22 CTF Qualifiers are in the books. Challenges were faced, and bested. Points were accumulated. Bedtimes were missed. It’s all over but the paperwork.</p>

<p>So here’s a roundup of writeup links. IF you participated, read and see how other people approached the same problems. If you didn’t, read and get an idea of how the CTF process works and consider signing up next time. You lose 100% of the CTFs you don’t enter. </p>

<p>If you enter, you could still lose 100%. That’s just math. But you’ll have a story. An awesome, glorious, highly technical story to share with the tiny slice of humanity who can understand this sort of thing.</p>

<p>There’s also a bonus link to a GitHub collection that looks like it might end up pretty comprehensive.</p>

<p>
<a href="https://hackucf.org/blog/category/writeups/defcon-quals-2014-writeups/">https://hackucf.org/blog/category/writeups/defcon-quals-2014-writeups/</a><br>

<a href="http://blog.spiderlabs.com/2014/05/defcon-22-ctf-qualifiers-writeup.html">http://blog.spiderlabs.com/2014/05/defcon-22-ctf-qualifiers-writeup.html</a><br>

<a href="http://balidani.blogspot.com/2014/05/def-con-quals-2014-100lines-writeup.html">http://balidani.blogspot.com/2014/05/def-con-quals-2014-100lines-writeup.html</a><br>

<a href="http://ahack.ru/write-ups/defcon-quals-14.htm">http://ahack.ru/write-ups/defcon-quals-14.htm</a><br>

<a href="http://zepvn.com/blog/defcon-ctf-quals-2014-100lines.php">http://zepvn.com/blog/defcon-ctf-quals-2014-100lines.php</a><br>

<a href="http://zepvn.com/blog/defcon-ctf-quals-2014-byhd.php">http://zepvn.com/blog/defcon-ctf-quals-2014-byhd.php</a><br>

<a href="http://sigint.ru/writeups/2014/05/19/defcon-2014-quals---zombies/">http://sigint.ru/writeups/2014/05/19/defcon-2014-quals---zombies/</a><br>

<a href="http://sigint.ru/writeups/2014/05/18/defcon-2014-quals--polyglot/">http://sigint.ru/writeups/2014/05/18/defcon-2014-quals--polyglot/</a><br>

<a href="http://endgame.com/blog/defcon-capture-the-flag-qualification-challenge-1.html">http://endgame.com/blog/defcon-capture-the-flag-qualification-challenge-1.html</a><br>

<a href="https://github.com/ctfs/write-ups/tree/master/def-con-ctf-qualifier-2014</p>">https://github.com/ctfs/write-ups/tree/master/def-con-ctf-qualifier-2014</a></p>

]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2014 16:05:33 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2C1BAFFA-0DBE-4A92-A01C-03E989F77814</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>On your mark... Get set...</title>
            <link>https://blog.legitbs.net/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/ctf-monument.jpg" alt="CTF temple">

<p>T minus 3 hours - DEF CON 22 CTF Qualifications are upon us! To read up on the setup for this year, you can check out the Legitimate Business Syndicate blog:</p>

<p><a href="https://blog.legitbs.net/">https://blog.legitbs.net/</a></p>

<p>The road to glory begins here. We at DEF CON applaud all of the brave warriors who've accepted the CTF challenge. Godspeed. May the odds be ever in your favor.</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 16:03:54 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4CCD73F9-EAD9-46EB-88F0-D31A301A175E</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Big New Batch of Talks Incoming!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-news.html#dc22speakers3</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/mic-drop.jpg" alt="Hand Dropping mic"></figure>
                    
<p>Don’t look now, but it’s already the middle of May. DEF CON 22 is just over the horizon, a little less than three months away. Preparations are in high gear.</p>

<p>Today, we bring you  more talks - 15 more, to be exact. You can check out the abstracts and speaker bios on the DC22 speaker page. We think you’ll like the choices - there’s everything from shortwave radio steganography to mischief with car firmware.</p> 

<p>There’s more coming, of course, so keep checking back with our speaker page as we flesh out the roster. </p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html</a></p>

<p>The new selections are:</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Campbell">The Secret Life of Krbtgt</a><br>	
Christopher Campbell</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Campbell2">The $env:PATH less Traveled is Full of Easy Privilege Escalation Vulns</a><br>
Christopher Campbell</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Dorsey">Why Don’t You Just Tell Me Where The ROP Isn’t Suppose To Go</a><br>
David Dorsey</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Drapeau">Steganography in Commonly Used HF Radio Protocols</a><br>
Paul Drapeau and Brent Dukes</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Macaulay">Weird-Machine Motivated Practical Page Table Shellcode & Finding Out What's Running on Your System</a><br>
Shane Macaulay</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Ossmann">The NSA Playset: RF Retroreflectors</a><br>
Michael Ossmann</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Ozavci">Attacking to Cisco Hosted VoIP Networks</a><br>
Fatih Ozavci</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Pickett">Abusing Software Defined Networks</a><br>
Gregory Pickett</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Polstra2">Am I Being Spied On? Low-tech Ways Of Detecting High-tech Surveillance</a><br>
Dr. Phil Polstra</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Schrenk">You're Leaking Trade Secrets</a><br>
Michael Schrenk</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Seeley">Zends Dead baby</a><br>
Dr Steven Seeley</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Tal">I Hunt TR-069 Admins: Pwning ISPs Like a Boss</a><br>
Shahar Tal</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Wardle">Optical Surgery; Implanting a DropCam</a><br>
Patrick Wardle and Colby Moore</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Zacharis">PoS Attacking the Traveling Salesman</a><br>
Alex Zacharis</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#0x222">Playing with Car Firmware or How to Brick your Car</a><br>
Paul 0x222</strong></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 09:22:15 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1A17E6DF-2DF0-4450-A599-66C316D05532</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>More Accepted Talks!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/mic-drop.jpg" alt="Hand Dropping mic"></figure>

                    
<p>We’re hard at working choosing the best of the CFP submissions, and today we have five more confirmations to announce. Watch this space for more speaker announcements in the coming weeks. It’s shaping up to be a pretty fascinating roster.</p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Bloxham">Getting Windows to Play with Itself: A Hacker's Guide to Windows API Abuse</a><br>
Brady Bloxham</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Jauregui">Girl… Fault-Interrupted.</a><br>
Maggie Jauregui</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Deviant">Elevator Hacking - From the Pit to the Penthouse</a><br>
Deviant Ollam, Howard Payne</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Shapiro">Hacking the FBI: How &amp; Why to Liberate Government Records</a><br>
Ryan Noah Shapiro</strong></p>

<p><strong><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html#Thieme">The Only Way to Tell the Truth is in Fiction: The Dynamics of Life in the National Security State</a><br>
Richard Thieme</strong></p>

<p>You can watch the conference taking shape on the DEF CON Speaker Page:<br>

<a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html">https://defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html</a></p>

]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 14:41:33 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">13870BE0-3237-4296-B5AF-774170A65EF7</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Art Contest Winners!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-artwork-contest.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/ac-montage.jpg" alt="Montage of past Artwork Contest entries"></figure>

<p>Congratulations to the winners of the DC 22 Art Contest:</p>

<p>1st Place: Alice in Hackerland by Tess Schrodinger<br>
2nd Place: Helicopter Parents Weren’t This Bad by Amit Yehuda<br>
3rd Place: Bleed by Joey Strine</p>

<p>People’s Choice: Alice in Hackerland by Tess Schrodinger</p>

<p>And of course, thanks to everyone who submitted work. There is no end to the hidden talents of the DEF CON massive. You can check out the winning artwork on the DC Art Contest page:<br>
<a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-artwork-contest.html">https://defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-artwork-contest.html</a></p>


<p>And a gallery of all the entries at:<br>
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10152137558786656.1073741846.90487656655&type=1">https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a....</a></p>

<p>Also, don’t let the contest ending stop you - if you have the urge to create some on-theme artworks between now and the show, we’d be happy to share them with the world. You won’t win anything beyond our love and gratitude, but that’s not exactly nothing.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 14:43:28 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D9112279-8806-47B3-A55F-F0078F7D3A0D</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Vote for People's Choice in the DEF CON 22 Artwork Contest!</title>
            <link>https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10152137558786656.1073741846.90487656655&amp;type=1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/ac-montage.jpg" alt="Montage of past Artwork Contest entries"></figure>               

<p>The DEF CON 22 art contest has closed, and it’s time to start picking the winners. In the ‘People’s Choice’ category, that means it’s time for YOU to cast a vote. Check out the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10152137558786656.1073741846.90487656655&type=1">Artwork Contest Entries Gallery</a> on Facebook and cast a ‘Like’ for your favorite.</p>

<p>The winner gets free admission to DC22, $25 credit at the Swag Booth and inky immortality in the DC22 printed program, so it’s kind of a big deal. The theme was ‘Behind the Curtain’, and the winning work should in some way capture the sense of the hidden world behind the world that is seen. Cast your votes wisely.</p>

<p>And as always, we thank everyone who participated in this year’s contest. If you didn’t submit and you’re feeling a little jelly, we offer the wise words of Socrates, who said to his students, “He is not wise who playa-hates; the truly wise participate. This mimosa is terrible.”</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 12:32:37 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3CEC2D5B-0EBA-4136-884A-68615421447D</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Vendor FAQ and App is Now Live!</title>
            <link>http://defconvendors.com/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/vendors.jpg" alt="Vendor vending"></figure>

<p>Attention Entreprenerds!</p>

<p>DEF CON 22’s Vendor Area is a great opportunity to get your geek-centric product in front of a highly focused, upwardly mobile and possibly drunk audience of over 10,000 vacationing tech enthusiasts. Share your business with people passionate about technology, make sales, even make friends.</p> 

<p>To sign up, head over to the vendor site, read the FAQ and get the forms filled out. Don’t delay - August is closer than you think.</p>

<p><a href="http://defconvendors.com/">http://defconvendors.com/</a>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 14:02:30 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">28F0B4E1-4F2F-458D-A68F-4CFBEE35FDCB</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Call for Papers &amp;mdash; Only Two Weeks Left!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/cfp-reminder.jpg" alt="Smiley with a string tied to its finger"></figure>

<p>Friendly reminder - the DEF CON 22 CFP closes in two short weeks. Your submission has to be in by May 1. It’s go time, people.</p>

<p>To see what we’ve accepted so far, you can check the speaker page:<br>
<a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html</a></p>

<p>The rules and regulations are here:<br>
<a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp.html">https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp.html</a></p>

<p>If you’ve got a great idea, put it in the ring. You can’t win if you don’t play.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 11:59:03 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ED477DFF-30D9-43E6-BBE8-C378AA117710</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Speaker Page Posted, Check Out the First Round Accepted!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/mic-drop.jpg" alt="Hand Dropping mic"></figure>
 
<p>It's official. CON season is really upon us. </p>

<p>DEF CON HQ is proud to announce the <a href="../defcon-22/dc-22-speakers.html">first round of accepted speakers</a>! Take a look, let us know what you think and what you're looking forward to most. We'd also love it if you kept your eye on the speaker page, because we'll be posting the rest of the accepted speakers as they are selected.  On the speaker page you can watch DEF CON 22 taking shape, and you can weigh in here or <a href="https://twitter.com/_defcon_">@_defcon_</a>.</p> 

<p>We think you're gonna like the choices so far. Get excited - the countdown has begun!</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 14:08:34 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">52FFD31C-5CD6-4473-B0B2-FD1F10661B98</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>SECTF Registration is Live!</title>
            <link>http://www.social-engineer.org/ctf/def-con-22-sectf-registration-rules/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-sectf.jpg" alt="SECTF Logo"></figure>

<p>The Social Engineering Capture the Flag contest is back for DEF CON 22 - this time with a Tag Team Twist! Spread the word and get signed up if you're ready to test your SE skills in Vegas!</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 17:13:34 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">B55329DB-53D0-45EC-A249-C9B862B790F0</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Faces of DEF CON</title>
            <link>http://eddietheyeti.deviantart.com/gallery/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/facesofdefcon.jpg" alt="Samples of the Faces of DEF CON artwork by Eddie the Yeti"> </figure>              

<p>Our community never fails to amaze. With no prompting from anyone, Eddie the Yeti has been making these beautiful portraits of DEF CON's better known faces and sharing them with the subjects. </p>

<p>He makes them with materials like soy sauce and coffee, wine and lime juice. He makes them insanely fast, but he still manages to get across the best of the subject's personality.</p>

<p>Check out his Faces of DEF CON series on DeviantArt. Check out the rest of his work, too. He's as good an advertisement as there could be for why you should come hang out with us in the desert. Brilliant, generous and doing it for the love.</p>

<p>Thanks, Eddie. </p>

<p><a href="http://eddietheyeti.deviantart.com/gallery/" title="Eddie the Yeti on DeviantArt">http://eddietheyeti.deviantart.com/gallery/</a></p>

<p>Pilgrim, another DEF CON regular, has made a tribute site to the series as well, at</p>

<p><a href="http://www.facesofdefcon.org/" title="Faces of DEF CON site by Pilgrim">http://www.facesofdefcon.org/</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 15:02:46 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02D9833A-77CB-4B53-9FEC-CD182FF4E4E6</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The DEF CON 22 site is open!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-index.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-web.jpg" alt="DEF CON 22 Logo"></figure>

<p>Good news, everyone!</p>

<p>It’s hard to believe, but we’re already two-thirds of the way to DEF CON 22. </p>

<p>As we come down the home stretch, the <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-index.html" title="DEF CON 22 Website">DEF CON 22 site</a> will be your one-stop information center for everything DC22. We’ll be constantly updating the site with talks, contests, events, entertainers and announcements to help you get the most out of your con.</p>

<p>Throw us a bookmark and keep checking back. Make us a regular part of your balanced media breakfast, and we’ll keep you up to date on everything you need to know.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2014 11:20:41 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">AD5A931C-1851-4B52-BFAE-81385195FA61</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 CTF: Registration is Open!</title>
            <link>https://blog.legitbs.net/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/ctfregannounce.png" alt="Keep calm and play ctf image"></figure>
                
<p>Good news, everyone!</p>

<p>Registration for the DEF CON 22 CTF season is open! To accomodate international competitors, the qualifying weekend has been moved to May 17-19.</p> 

<p>It is time to assemble your champions. Sharpen them to a fine point. The doors to the arena open May 17. Fortune looks kindly upon boldness and skill. Failing those, she also seems pretty okay with treachery and subversion.</p>

<p>The information you require can be found at <a href="https://blog.legitbs.net/">https://blog.legitbs.net/</a> . You can register at <a href="https://2014.legitbs.net/">https://2014.legitbs.net/</a>.
</p>
<p>Step forward and meet your destiny.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 14:06:20 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A847ABF5-7B8B-48D9-8E75-26BA26C7AF7F</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The DEF CON 22 Contests, Events and Villages RFI is Now Open!</title>
            <link>http://defcne.net/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/cneannounce.png" alt="Image of DEF CON gameshow"></figure>
               
<p>Got an idea for a game-changing contest or event? Maybe you have the expertise to run a village on a compelling topic we've overlooked? This is your moment. Submit your idea on the DEF CON CnE website - we'll partner up with the best ideas and help make them happen.</p>

<p>The rules and guidelines are available on the CnE website. Check them out, and get yourself involved. We look forward to hearing your ideas.</p>

<p><a href="http://defcne.net/">http://defcne.net/</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 11:40:37 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">CF355BDB-6B51-4316-84E3-A21CF35DC892</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DC22 Artwork Contest: Only Two Weeks Left!</title>
            <link>https://defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-artwork-contest.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://defcon.org/images/defcon-main/ac-montage.jpg" alt="montage of past art contest winners"></figure>
               
<p>We know that art takes time. We know that artists like to paint themselves into deadline corners, waiting until the last minute for inspiration to strike. If that's you, please bear in mind that the minutes run out in about two weeks. If you want to have your work considered for the contest, it has to be in to us by April 10. No exceptions.</p>

<p>Also, if you know a creative soul who might enjoy the opportunity, be sure to share this with them. We'd really love to showcase a lot of cool work this year.</p>

<p>Relevant data is all here:<br>
<a href="https://defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-artwork-contest.html">https://defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-artwork-contest.html</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 15:53:50 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">32AE4162-03F3-44C0-B678-0FE57A88662D</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Be the Match returning to DEF CON 22!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dc22bethematch</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/btm.jpg" alt="Image of Be the Match sign-up form"></figure>
 
<p>For the 4th year, 'Be the Match' is returning to DEF CON. It's your opportunity to register as a Bone Marrow Donor, and maybe someday save a life. There are lots of ways to hack your body, but this one doesn't slow you down at airports or make you look sketchy.</p> 
<p>It also makes you kind of a hero. </p>

<p>To find out more about how 'Be the Match' works, you can check them out at these links:</p>

<p>Twitter: @bethematch<br>
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/BeTheMatch">https://www.facebook.com/BeTheMatch</a><br>
The InterTubes: <a href="http://bethematch.org/">http://bethematch.org/</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 10:33:02 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">64714979-E410-4411-B881-8713016E4985</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Artwork Contest!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-artwork-contest.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/ac-montage.jpg" alt="Montage of past Artwork Contest entries"></figure>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-artwork-contest.html" title="DEF CON 22 Artwork Contest!">DEF CON Art Contest is back!</a></p>

<p>The theme of this year's art contest is "Behind the Curtain". Secrets. Lies. Alibis. The magic shades in 'They Live'. The world behind the world, where all the hidden gears are turning.  The code and subterfuge employed by the adept to sneak knowledge past the sleeping and the uninitiated.</p>

<p>Cool, right? If you can put together a jaw-dropping variation on that theme in the next 30 days, prizes and glory could be yours. Free admissions to DEF CON 22, credit to burn on DEF CON Swag, maybe even a T-shirt with your art on it.</p>

<p>There are Categories and Rules, of course. And a Deadline. All of these are important.  These things make it a contest. But you, my undercover artist friend, you make it epic. Pencils up and good luck.</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 14:31:55 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">35540734-02D2-4C4F-AC6F-267AD80DA9BD</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Call for Musicians/Artists/DJs application is LIVE!</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=13776</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/dj.jpg" alt="DEF CON DJ Photo"></figure>
               
<p>If you're a musical performer, a DJ or an ambient Esperanto slam poet* who dreams of performing at DEF CON, this is your moment. We're beginning to select music acts for DEF CON 22, and we might very well need YOU. </p>

<p>Extra slots for Chillout/Ambient/Downtempo types this year, so you lower-BPM types should make sure to apply. </p>

<p>Your road to rocking DEF CON starts with reading the rules.</p>

<p><a href="https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=13776">https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=13776</a></p>
 
<p>Then, if you think you have what it takes to entertain the DEF CON massive, fill out this form.
<a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1N0Kwl-o_KEoYmv72235oS6KLgLxmlgP35h_wjfjAIWk/viewform">https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1N0K...jAIWk/viewform</a></p>

<p>*I'm pretty sure I made that up, but I would be happy to be proved wrong. I will make you a Facebook star.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 14:12:27 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DBAA2810-BF20-48B9-96E2-EE174530231D</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Capture the Flag Pre-Qualification Events!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dc22qualifiers</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-ctf-2014.jpg" alt="Legitimate Business Syndicate image of hackers at CTF"></figure>

<p>CTF is coming.</p>

<p>Steep is the climb, and narrow the way to DEF CON’s ancient and storied CTF contest. Many will take up arms, but few will persevere to the final field of struggle. </p>

<p>To the victor, glory eternal. </p>

<p>Champions must possess matchless skill, dauntless courage and reckless disregard for the goddess Circadia and her infernal rhythms. They must also pre-qualify. </p>

<p>To that end, Legitimate Business Syndicate has posted the Pre-Qual Events list on the DEF CON website. Your journey begins there. </p>

<p>Godspeed, you magnificent bastards. Godspeed.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dc22qualifiers">https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dc22qualifiers</a></p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 14:32:16 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3C3E7E8C-9713-4538-840F-F2E72A17EACD</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON Future Dates!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-news.html#dcdatesfuture</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure><img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/calendar.png" alt="DEF CON Calendar icon"></figure>

<p>Sure, you know that DEF CON 22 rolls around August 7-10, 2014. Everyone knows that. But do you know the dates for DEF CON 23? DEF CON 24?</p>

<p>Probably not, because we're announcing it right now. DEF CON 23 will be August 6-9, 2015, and DEF CON 24 will be August 4-7, 2016.</p>

<p>Now you know. And knowing is half the battle.</p>
                ]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 10:40:28 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5E150072-EE47-41AA-A004-E57F98E05DD1</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Bank error in your favor!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#rioroomrate</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>When we announced the discount room rates for the Rio last month, there was some kind of glitch in the Matrix. The first 200 signups were granted a rate even lower than our block rate. The Keymaker at the Rio has agreed to honor this rate for those lucky registrants. He had the Architect explain it to me, but he droned on so long I lost the plot. What I can confirm is that the 200th registration was reached, the anomaly was smoothed over and real-world rates have returned.</p><br />
<figure><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/rio2-post.jpg" alt="Rio Hotel & Casino image"> </figure>
<p>As ever, Fortune favors the bold.</p> 
<p>The corrected rate (based on occupancy of up to three per room and taxed at 12%) is:<br />
Sunday -Thursday   $119.00<br />
Friday &amp; Saturday $129.00</p>
<p>They charge an extra $30 a night if you add a fourth. Sometimes it's worth it. We don't judge.</p>
<p>Even that rate won't last long – the DEF CON block is about 40% sold. To book now and get the block rate, follow this link. See how deep the rabbit hole goes.</p>
<p><a href="https://resweb.passkey.com/go/SRDEF4" title="Rio Room Link">https://resweb.passkey.com/go/SRDEF4</a>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 00:23:02 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">60C2059C-148B-4C53-B7B6-567684EB9594-7652-0000C9F1233D1103-FFA</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NEW! Announcing the DEF CON 22 Call for Services!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfs.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/cfs-illo.png" alt="DEF CON Call for Services comic">

<p>Got something cool to share on the DEF CON network during DC22? Could be almost anything - a game, a stash of vintage K-Rad textfiles, whatever you think Con goers might wanna download. Submit your idea online, and if it's approved you'll get a couple of bonded gig ports and some promotion in the program and on the site. Sharing is kinda our thing - and we're counting on you to add some fun content. <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfs.html">Apply today</a>. Operators are standing by.* <br><br>

* actual operator count may be as low as zero.

</p>
]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 14:33:59 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">19342601-46C7-49AD-AA9D-325451C6365B</guid>
            <media:thumbnail url="ttps://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/cfs-illo.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON is Now on Google+!</title>
            <link>https://google.com/+DefconOrgplus</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/g+-screen.jpg" alt="DEF CON on Google+ screen capture">

<p>We're starting up a presence on G+. We've got some interesting plans for the specific technologies they employ over there. If you're on G+ (and you probably are), come on over and add us to your circles. We can be found at <a href="https://google.com/+DefconOrgplus" title="DEF CON on Google+">https://google.com/+DefconOrgplus</a>.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 13:09:18 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">BBD3D6CC-7013-4A3E-93F0-042B35DA41D2</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 14 Video now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaAxDI0xo83ZFzDAZgXO3YhyL</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img class="postImage scale-with-grid" src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-14/dc-14-media-sq.png" alt="DEF CON 14 Logo"> 

<p>Can't stop, won't stop! New playlist up on YouTube, this time <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaAxDI0xo83ZFzDAZgXO3Yhy">the entirety of DEF CON 14</a>. Over 80 presentations. You can fire it up right now and be edutained for the next two weeks or so. </p>

<p>We'd love it if you'd share the knowledge with anyone you think might benefit. Like, share and be merry.</p>]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 15:26:04 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">366FAF4B-9E14-44A6-B303-5A05BB9BC941</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 15 Video now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaCji1aEQBUrIpPQf9-HazLL</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-15/dc-15-media-sq.jpg" alt="DEF CON 15 logo" height="400" width="400"/><br /><br />

<a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaCji1aEQBUrIpPQf9-HazLL">Re-live all DEF CON 15 had to offer</a> on our YouTube channel, we have a new playlist posted for your enjoyment!]]></description>
            <author>feedback@defcon.org (DEF CON Announcements)</author>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 13:15:33 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2F046C9C-5973-4AC4-BC02-FD47E8DDE364</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Short Story Contest!</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=13755</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<figure>
<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/ssc.gif" alt="Short Story Contest Logo" style="padding-right: 15px;" data-fl-original-src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/ssc.gif"/>
</figure>
<p>The DEF CON Short Story Contest is back, and it's already open! No excuses - you have from now until the first of June to get your story in for the chance to win some cool prizes and get your story shared with the whole DC community. Four months to shape your hacker lit masterpiece. Make us proud.</p>

<p>The rules and regulations are all available in the <a href="https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=13755">Short Story Contest thread on the DC Forums.</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 11:51:36 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">EB4BCB19-B530-4D1E-9FDA-2DDDA910CC47</guid>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/ssc.gif"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 Audio now on iTunes!</title>
            <link>https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/def-con-21-audio-speeches/id806242602?mt=2&amp;uo=4</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-21/dc-21-audio-400.gif" alt="DEF CON 21 Audio Artwork" data-fl-original-src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-21/dc-21-audio-400.gif"/></p>

<p>Good News! <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/def-con-21-audio-speeches/id806242602?mt=2&uo=4" target="itunes_store">Audio from all the presentations at DEF CON 21</a> is now available as a podcast for those who prefer their DEF CON goodness in a smooth, iTunes-digestible format. Lyric files included on the house. Enjoy and spread the word!</p>

<p>The direct link to the podcast is <a href="https://www.defcon.org/podcast/defcon-21-audio.rss">https://www.defcon.org/podcast/defcon-21-audio.rss</a></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 16:14:30 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">68D01BC3-61ED-4D04-9E36-6ADF86D529AA</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 Call for Papers is Now Open!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp.jpg" width="650" alt="DEF CON Call For Papers header image" data-fl-original-src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp.jpg"/>

<p>It's that time again folks! Polish up those ninja caliber proposals, because The <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-22/dc-22-cfp.html">DEF CON Call for Papers</a> is now officially open! Read the announcement and find out what's new, then fill out the CFP form and start down the road to DEF CON glory! Good luck!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 16:14:52 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">96487532-2140-4FF8-B230-9F3B8E79A29B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 Audio Files Are Now Live for Torrent or Download!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#dc21audio</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-21/dc-21-audio-400.gif" alt="DEF CON 21 Audio Artwork" data-fl-original-src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-21/dc-21-audio-400.gif"/>

<p>Hear the sweet sounds of hackers imparting their knowledge in the DEF CON 21 audio speeches, now available for download on the <a href="https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON 21/DEF CON 21 audio/" title="DEF CON 21 Audio on the DEF CON Media Server">DEF CON Media Server</a>, The <a href="html/links/dc-archives/dc-21-archive.html" title="DEF CON 21 Archive Page">DEF CON 21 Archive page</a>, or all at once with this handy torrent:</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 audio.torrent" title="DEF CON 21 Audio Torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 audio.torrent</a></p>

<p>Also included, and new this year, are .lrc format transcripts which can be used as lyrics files for the audio, Enjoy!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 11:19:31 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">C94598F9-4085-40FB-8B96-6A50BF5F498B</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2014 DEF CON Groups Challenge!</title>
            <link>https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=13743</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/defcon-20-badges.jpg" alt="DEF CON 20 Badges" data-fl-original-src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/defcon-20-badges.jpg"/>

<p>We have seen DC 21 come and go, and after a little rest we all have begun preparing ourselves for DC22. Since we have 7 months until we all meet again in Vegas, I have prepared a fun contest to help you pass the time. </p>

<p>Plus, if you win, you and your team mates will get free badges (8 free badges for 1st, 4 free badges for second) to help offset the costs of attending DC22!</p>

<p>Have fun and happy hacking!</p>

<p>-blak </p>

<p><a href="https://forum.defcon.org/showthread.php?t=13743">Read all about the 2014 DEF CON Groups Challenge!</a></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 12:57:37 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6F5AA042-E343-4259-B9FE-9B885695C874</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 videos now available for direct download and torrent!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#dc21video</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-21/dc-21-video-400.gif" alt="DEF CON 21 Video Artwork" data-fl-original-src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-21/dc-21-video-400.gif"/>

<p>Did you miss DEF CON 21? Do you have a ridiculous amount of hard drive space and like to keep large archives of hacking knowledge? At long last, all of the DEF CON 21 speeches can be found on the <a href="html/links/dc-archives/dc-21-archive.html" title="DEF CON 21 Archive page">DEF CON 21 Archive page</a>, The <a href="https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON 21/" title="DEF CON 21 on the DEF CON Media server">DEF CON Media Server</a>, or downloaded en masse at these torrents:</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 video and slides.torrent " title="DEF CON 21 Video and Slides torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 video and slides.torrent </a>
<br />
<a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 slides.torrent" title="DEF CON 21 Slides Video torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 slides.torrent</a></p>

<p>For the fist time ever, we have transcripts of the talks! Use them for closed captioning, read them, or if you are feeling saucy, translate them to other languages and be sure to let us know!</p>

<p>Enjoy!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 16:16:40 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">377C2E48-DC9B-4D50-94F5-7256338382FC</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Book a room at the Rio for DEF CON 22!</title>
            <link>https://resweb.passkey.com/go/SRDEF4</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/rio2-post.jpg" alt="Image of the Rio Hotel" data-fl-original-src="https://www.defcon.org/images/defcon-main/rio2-post.jpg"/>

<p>For those of you that want to get a jump on DEF CON 22, you can now <a href="https://resweb.passkey.com/go/SRDEF4" title="Book a room at the Rio for DEF CON 22">book your room for DEF CON 22 at our discounted rate</a>! Register now and save! We have a special discount for the first 200 reservations made in the DEF CON block. There are still a few left, so jump in now and stay at our host venue for the full DEF CON Experience!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 10:26:03 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">995A36D1-FEE3-4736-BFD7-473B1D63EA11</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Announcing DEF CON 22 CTF!</title>
            <link>https://blog.legitbs.net/2014/01/announcing-def-con-22-capture-flag.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Legitimate Business Syndicate has announced their intention to return as organizers of the Capture the Flag competition! Check out their <a href="https://blog.legitbs.net/2014/01/announcing-def-con-22-capture-flag.html" title="DEF CON 22 CTF Announcement">DEF CON 22 CTF Announcement</a> blog post!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 10:29:18 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8C03A4C5-50FE-45F6-9685-452CCEFCC0A5</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Happy New Year from DEF CON!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#newyear2014</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>We would like to wish all hackers, geeks, techs, nerds, makers, phreaks, engineers, privacy and security folks the world over a Happy New Year!</p>

<p>2014 will be a year of security battles, with more companies responding to news of their products being used in mass monitoring. Now is the time to get involved!</p>

<p>The IETF is working on the possibility of HTTP 2.0 requiring TLS always, dramatically encrypting more of the Web. Why wait?</p>

<ul>
<li>Enable HSTS on your own sites, enable EDH as well for "perfect forward secrecy"</li>

<li>Run a tor server as middle if you don't want to be and exit. This is what we do.</li>

<li>Encrypt your email. Don't want to fight with PGP? Then install an S/MIME certificate. IPhones work with them really well too.</li>

<li>Encrypt your sms messages. Check out Wickr on Android and iPhone, or try "text secure" on Android, it should be on iPhone soon.</li>
</ul>

<p>You guys get the idea. Make a resolution to up your defense game in 2014 to make life more difficult for all who would eavesdrop on us - for whatever reason.</p>

<p>Oh, and Hack the Planet™</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 19:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1F08E390-43E4-4674-B3DB-1918C26DD31A</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Happy Holidays! DEF CON 21 Videos Now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBD_8E9PJ8yyiTL0JhynlGK</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Just in time for the holidays, we have a long awaited Christmas/Hanukkah/Kwanzaa/Festivus/Solstice/etc. gift for all of you! <a href="http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBD_8E9PJ8yyiTL0JhynlGK" title="DEF CON 21 on YouTube">You can now watch all of the DEF CON 21 talks on YouTube</a>, with or without closed captioning! That's right, go ahead and stream all the hacker-y goodness from this year's DEF CON with your favorite holiday beverage in front of a warm fire! Happy Holidays from all of us at DEF CON!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 21:14:05 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">89894C2C-A00F-47BD-872C-04B805368302</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 CTF Packet Captures from Saturday!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF%20CON%2021%20ctf%20saturday.torrent</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Well here it is, the biggest one yet! <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 ctf saturday.torrent" title="DEF CON 21 CTF packet captures - Saturday">Complete packet captures from Saturday at the DEF CON 21 Capture the Flag</a> competition are now available for torrent!  This is a huge one folks, compressed down to 35 gigs from 495, so get those hard drives cleared out and ready!</p>

<p>If you can, leave them seeding for a bit to share the love!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 14:13:04 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D89FEAF8-1BCA-4901-9141-FEB8E3B7E2F5</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 CTF Packet Captures from Sunday!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF%20CON%2021%20ctf%20sunday.torrent</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All of you CTF-ophiles out there, rejoice! <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 ctf sunday.torrent" title="DEF CON 21 CTF packet captures - Sunday">Complete packet captures from Sunday at the DEF CON 21 Capture the Flag</a> competiton are now available for torrent!  Sift through all the data and peer at the inner workings of the contest!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 11:53:42 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5FEFE29E-38F7-4E48-90D7-559DB179E68C</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 16 Videos now on YouTube! </title>
            <link>http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBY3OjTaGyaBzgc80sOFkG8</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here's something to be thankful for! We've now posted the <a href="http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBY3OjTaGyaBzgc80sOFkG8" title="DEF CON 16 Speeches on YouTube">complete DEF CON 16 speeches</a> on YouTube to watch at your leisure! Enjoy!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 14:45:33 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">F8DC3AE0-B10D-47D2-AB38-3418721A7F0E</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 17 Videos now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaDjnjDsjgmtASOWg8a8neEE</link>
            <description><![CDATA[You can now stream all the <a href="http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaDjnjDsjgmtASOWg8a8neEE" title="DEF CON 17 YouTube Playlist">videos from DEF CON 17</a> that your heart desires on YouTube, the latest installment to our channel! Enjoy!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 11:39:01 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">AA060150-F241-4F1A-BC5F-300E8F4AA2EF</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON CTF in the News!</title>
            <link>http://www.cnbc.com/id/101179977/page/1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Check out this <a href="http://www.cnbc.com/id/101179977/page/1">recent article from CNBC on the DEF CON 21 CTF Competition</a>!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 16:42:15 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">17EAC89F-C6FB-43D7-B9A0-E5225881EBFB</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 18 Videos now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaC26TgwyDg2Db-m5E7jRRbj</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaC26TgwyDg2Db-m5E7jRRbj">DEF CON 18 Presentations have been added to the DEF CON YouTube</a>! If you're looking for a laugh, Zoz's presentation will cheer you up. </p>

<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jwpg-AwJ0Jc&list=PL9fPq3eQfaaC26TgwyDg2Db-m5E7jRRbj" title="DEF CON 18 Zoz Presentation">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jwpg-AwJ0Jc&amp;list=PL9fPq3eQfaaC26TgwyDg2Db-m5E7jRRbj </a></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 13:46:26 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7C282560-34D0-47DD-BE14-6D3A1473D2AC</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 19 Videos now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBoESMifnn5w4S487vrmGR6</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<a href="http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaBoESMifnn5w4S487vrmGR6">DEF CON 19 videos are now live on YouTube</a> for your streaming pleasure.  We hope you enjoy these videos, and if you do please "like" them. Comments are open, so feel free to leave feedback, or start a conversation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 16:40:49 -0800</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">742D373C-6DA6-4C6E-92C2-C77F768596EB</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 20 Videos now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaDcbIEMSzdL5yuzh_m6BB-E</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The massive upload has begun! We are currently in the process of uploading all of the DEF CON video from past years to our YouTube Channel, and we begin with DEF CON 20! We're getting them up en masse and processed as we speak, and will be releasing them as we finish each show. Next up will be DEF CON 19. We hope you will enjoy them!
<br />  
<br />  <a href="http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL9fPq3eQfaaDcbIEMSzdL5yuzh_m6BB-E" title="DEF CON 20 Presentations - Video + Slides playlist on Youtube">DEF CON 20 Presentations - Video + Slides playlist on Youtube</a></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 13:35:48 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2DB80B9B-DCB9-4EF6-B771-4B27358A35C3</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 22 CTF Quals Tentative Dates Announced!  </title>
            <link>https://legitbs.net/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The team over at Legitimate Business Syndicate is getting a jump on things for DEF CON 22, and have announced their tentative dates for the 2014 CTF Quals! The 2014 Quals will be held Midnight May 17 to Midnight May 19, 1400284800 to 1400457600. Keep an eye on <a href="https://legitbs.net">https://legitbs.net</a> for all of their updates, and for links to the LegitBS Blog and twitter feed!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 10:33:22 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">43837CB4-107D-45A2-9B34-1AA1B3717759</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 Photo Collections!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#dc21photos</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Have you never been to DEF CON or just want to re-live the precious memories from DEF CON 21? If so, we've posted some picture collections on media.defcon.org at <a href="http://media.defcon.org/DEF CON 21/DEF CON 21 pictures/" title="DEF CON 21 Pictures">http://media.defcon.org/DEF CON 21/DEF CON 21 pictures/</a>, or if you are of the torrenting sort, you can siphon them down all at once at:
<br /> 
<br />
<a href="html/torrent/DEF CON 21 pictures 1.torrent" title="DEF CON 21 Pictures 1 torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 pictures 1.torrent</a>
<br />
<a href="html/torrent/DEF CON 21 pictures 2.torrent" title="DEF CON 21 Pictures 2 torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 pictures 2.torrent</a>
<br />  
<br />Enjoy!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 10:41:34 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">38D569C0-CD84-4589-B277-7AB2A719A4BA</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 CTF Packet Captures from Friday + Tools and Binaries!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#dc21ctfpcapsfriday</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Legitimate Business Syndicate has been gracious enough to provide us with complete packet captures from the DEF CON 21 Capture the Flag contest! A big thanks to them and all the great teams who participated! Here is the first batch of those pcaps, <a href="html/torrent/DEF CON 21 ctf friday.torrent">all the traffic from Friday</a> at the con. Saturday and Sunday's will be soon to follow so keep your eyes peeled!
<br />  
<br />They were also so kind as to include the <a href="html/torrent/DEF CON 21 ctf binaries and tools.torrent">tools and binaries from the game</a>, which we have also included in a handy torrent file!
<br />  
<br />You can always find write-ups, file collections, and history of the DEF CON Capture the Flag competition on our <a href="html/links/dc-ctf.html">CTF Page</a>! Enjoy!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 16:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">DB277858-3A49-4058-B259-BACA3E3754E4</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 Materials RSS Feed, Updated CD, and Torrents!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#dc21materials</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>For all of you fine folks out there, we have lovingly compiled the speaker's slide decks and extras from the con CD into the <a href="podcast/defcon-21-materials.rss" title="DEF CON 21 Materials RSS feed">DEF CON 21 Materials RSS feed</a> for your enjoyment! Not only that, but it includes all the updates submitted by the speakers since the con, so you'll have all the latest research! So check it out and grab the stuff you are interested in!
<br />  
<br />  Alternatively, if you just gotta have it all sitting on a hard drive awaiting your whim, We have also posted a torrent and direct download link to the Updated Conference CD!
<br />  
<br />  We've also updated a couple of the large collection torrents, one for the DEF CON CD/DVD collection from all the shows to reflect the addition of DEF CON 21, and another for the Hacker Related Documentaries with the addition of DEF CON: The Documentary.
<br />  
<br />  Check out the following links and enjoy!
<br />  
<br />  <strong>DEF CON 21 Hacking Conference Updated CD (Final)</strong>
<br />
<a href="html/torrent/DEF CON 21 updated hacking conference CD.rar.torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 updated hacking conference CD.rar.torrent</a>
<br />
<a href="https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON Conference CD DVD/DEF CON 21 Updated Hacking Conference CD.rar">https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON Conference CD DVD/DEF CON 21 Updated Hacking Conference CD.rar</a></p>

<p><strong>DEF CON 21 Hacking Conference Presentations</strong> (These are all the presentations
<br />from the speakers, but not the extras folder)
<br />
<a href="html/torrent/DEF CON 21 presentations.torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 21 presentations.torrent</a>
<br />
<a href="https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON 21/DEF CON 21 presentations/">https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON 21/DEF CON 21 presentations/</a></p>

<p><strong>UPDATED Collection of conference CD and DVDs</strong> - Now includes DEF CON 21
<br />original and updated CDs
<br />
<a href="html/torrent/DEF CON Conference CD DVD Collection 2013.torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON Conference CD DVD Collection 2013.torrent</a>
<br />
<a href="https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON Conference CD DVD/">https://media.defcon.org/DEF CON Conference CD DVD/</a></p>

<p><strong>UPDATED: Hacking Documentaries hosted at DEF CON</strong> - Now includes the DEF CON
<br />Documentary and sneak peek
<br />
<a href="html/torrent/DEF CON Hosted hacking related documentaries v2.torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON Hosted hacking related documentaries v2.torrent</a>
<br /><a href="https://media.defcon.org/Hacking Related Documentaries/">https://media.defcon.org/Hacking Related Documentaries/</a></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 15:03:13 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">D59786BC-8F11-4A9B-8B3B-1E4D35B07E6D</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>In Case You Didn't Know...</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#dcpastcontent</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>This may be old news to some of you, but we've noticed a lot of questions in the comments from the last few Facebook posts about where past DEF CON Content resides.  We have several outlets: </p>

<p><a href="https://media.defcon.org" title="DEF CON Media Server">https://media.defcon.org</a> is a directory browsable repository for all of our past content.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-torrent.html" title="DEF CON Torrents page">https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-torrent.html</a> for all of our torrent files. These are the huge collections for all-at-once downloading</p>

<p><a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-archives.html" title="DEF CON Archives Portal">https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-archives.html</a> is a portal to our archive pages by year.</p>

<p>These include audio, video, CTF files, artwork and a ton more! So if you didn't know, now you do. Pick your poison and enjoy!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 13:16:58 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2CEE60BA-C31F-4D62-8FA2-FDA4107E13FA</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON The Documentary USB Sets Still Available!</title>
            <link>http://hackerstickers.com/product/defcon-documentary-set/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hey, if you missed it the first time, good news, we've uncovered a box of DEF CON Documentary USB Key Edition Kits with lanyards! They are now available at <a href="http://hackerstickers.com/product/defcon-documentary-set/">http://hackerstickers.com/product/defcon-documentary-set/</a>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 12:10:12 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">81A21C45-669F-47BD-B860-B3118C874950</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 Early Release Video on YouTube!</title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/DEFCONConference/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We've posted a few tasty morsels of early release video for you on the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/DEFCONConference/">DEF CON YouTube Channel</a>! You can absorb Zoz's talk on Hacking Driverless Vehicles, Mudge's anecdotes of being a hacker inside the government, and Melissa Elliot's research on unintentional radio emissions! Enjoy!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 22:12:14 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">359E7B92-8770-4143-BE46-C5BF84EB7AAF</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 Contest Results!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-21/dc-21-contest-results.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Were you wondering how everyone placed at this year's DEF CON Contests? Wander on over to the <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-21/dc-21-contest-results.html" title="DEF CON 21 Contest Results">DEF CON 21 Contest Results</a> Page for all that have reported back so far!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 11:30:37 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">A73E7750-EE50-410C-8CED-1DC9DD489036</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 Archive Page!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-archives/dc-21-archive.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Now scribed in the book of ages known as the interwebs, is the <a href="html/links/dc-archives/dc-21-archive.html" title="DEF CON 21 Archive page">DEF CON 21 Archive</a>. You'll find links to press, the program, the receipt, and all of the latest updated speaker materials and extras from DEF CON 21. Keep watch on this archive, data from this year's con is still rolling in and it will be updated, as we receive it! Enjoy!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 14:44:28 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">204B4899-AF77-46FD-B895-03E7D74900FD</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Bonus Features now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/user/DEFCONConference</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Like any good movie, DEF CON: the Documentary has tons of footage that didn't make the final cut. Now you can enjoy some extra antics, interview footage and other cool stuff from the world's largest hacking conference in the 21 bonus clips we've added to the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/DEFCONConference" title="DEF CON YouTube Channel">DEF CON YouTube Channel</a>!  If you couldn't get enough of the documentary here is more! Enjoy!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 14:28:19 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">81882073-390B-4C52-A8E0-068F1E8C4396</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON: The Documentary Bonus Footage and Soundtrack Torrents!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/index.html#dcdocextras</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Here's a sweet little bundle of extras from the DEF CON Documentary for your enjoyment, in a couple of handy torrent files!
<br />  
<br />  <strong>DEF CON Documentary soundtrack</strong>: Check out the music from the artists (Zoe Blade, Broke For Free, Chris Zabriskie, Revolution Void, The Insiders, and others) that made the DEF CON Documentary soundtrack possible! <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 20 Documentary soundtrack.torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 20 Documentary soundtrack.torrent</a></p>

<p><strong>DEF CON Documentary extra bonus clips</strong>: 21 Extra clips that didn't make the documentary. Interviews, background stories, and past trivia. If you finished watching the DEF CON Documentary wanting more, here it is! <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 20 Documentary bonus clips.torrent">https://www.defcon.org/html/torrent/DEF CON 20 Documentary bonus clips.torrent</a></p>

<p>Don't forget to share the love and leave these seeding for a little while!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 11:56:49 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">791E0DC0-E92D-47AD-B926-C1CB840A7577</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Press page updated for DEF CON 21!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc_press/dc_press.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extra! Extra! Read all about it! <a href="https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc_press/dc_press.html" title="DEF CON Press Archive">The DEF CON Press page</a> has been updated with over 200 new articles on DEF CON 21! Sometimes they get it right, and sometimes they get it wrong, but it's all there for your discriminating perusal!  Enjoy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 12:15:49 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3204857C-3D21-46D4-B8BB-693BDB1D527E</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CTF Page Updated for DEF CON 21!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/links/dc-ctf.html</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Check out the <a href="html/links/dc-ctf.html" title="DEF CON CTF Archive">DEF CON CTF Archive</a> for write-ups and links to the LegitBS Scorebot SQL Dump from this year's Capture the Flag!]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 09:34:48 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2CF6E99E-22BB-436E-BD20-7266D7212DA7</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON: The Documentary is now on YouTube!</title>
            <link>http://youtu.be/SUhyeY0Fsvw</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Hey all! If you'd like to access DEF CON: The Documentary when you're off your main machine, we now have it posted to the official DEF CON YouTube Channel! English and Japanese subtitles available, with Chinese on the way! Keep watch on this channel in the future for more great content from DEF CON! </p>

<p>DEF CON: The Documentary on Youtube: <a href="http://youtu.be/SUhyeY0Fsvw" title="DEF CON: The Documentary on YouTube">http://youtu.be/SUhyeY0Fsvw</a></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 11:40:29 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">AD60574A-EFEF-4B17-9722-55918BEC08F0</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Congrats To DEF CON 21 CTF Winners!</title>
            <link>https://legitbs.net/</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A hearty congratulations to Plaid Parliament of Pwning for taking this year's CTF crown! Thank you to Legitimate Business Syndicate for running a great game! Head on over to <a href="https://legitbs.net/">legitbs.net</a> for the scoreboard of this year's Capture the Flag and a wrap up of the event.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 10:29:39 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4612B2E9-9916-49C4-9DDE-495B5B063534</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DEF CON 21 - The Official Soundtrack!</title>
            <link>http://music.gravitasrecordings.com/album/def-con-21-the-official-soundtrack</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to the huge success of DEF CON's 20th anniversary compilation, we've brought it back again and stepped up our game. This year, we present you with "DEF CON 21: The Official Soundtrack:" 20 tracks of pure nerd fuel for hacking. The compilation features many of the talented acts in attendance at the conference, like <strong>BT</strong> (seriously!), Faderhead (for real!), and far beyond that with generous submissions from the likes of PANTyRAiD and Gramatik.</p>

<p>As if that wasn't enough, this release is completely free/donation-based, with 100% of the generated revenue going straight to the Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF / <a href="http://eff.org">http://eff.org</a>), a 501(c)3 not-for-profit dedicated to protecting our Internet freedoms and privacy.</p>

<p>Get on over to the Gravitas Recordings (the awesome label donating their time, energy, PR skills, and distribution networks to the cause) Bandcamp release page to grab this sonic goodness, check the full track-list, and ***DONATE***! </p>

<p>LINK: <a href="http://music.gravitasrecordings.com/album/def-con-21-the-official-soundtrack">http://music.gravitasrecordings.com/album/def-con-21-the-official-soundtrack</a></p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 15:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9E8083D6-24C2-47C0-8D11-E2DC0A17EAF7</guid>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cheers to an awesome DEF CON 21!</title>
            <link>https://www.defcon.org/html/defcon-21/dc-21-news.html#dc21close</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Well folks, that's another DEF CON on the books, and it was a great one! We're starting to make it home, and gather contest results, press, content, photos, and everything else from a fantastic DEF CON 21, so keep an eye on this space, our <a href="https://twitter.com/_defcon_">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/defcon">Facebook</a> in the coming days and weeks as it is scribed into the archives!</p>

<p>Big thanks to all of the attendees, You give us the reason to do this every year, and we're ecstatic that you travel to the middle of the desert in the dead of summer to enjoy our gathering!  To all of the goons, your tireless efforts and dedication shine year after year as we move through each and every con, thank you all.  A big thank you all of those who contribute their time, enthusiasm, knowledge, and talent to DEF CON through speaking, performing, and running contests, events, villages, and parties.</p>

<p>Stay tuned, and we hope to see you all at DEF CON 22!</p>]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 15:25:08 -0700</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">75B24693-DE90-4A56-B85A-953C2636F6EA</guid>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>